The voice without a body is called
Rosso, the feather cuts the darkness
whose sun dawns inside the room
Hey, next to you there?
Were those on my live?
Yeah, I think it might have privated them.
Hey, free site, how are you?
I'll be like, song, that was awesome.
I'm blown away right now.
Hey, Skies, the limit with the creativity,
it's like, I just get more and more ideas.
So how's your night? Oh, what is it? Is it Saturday? Oh, it's already Sunday. Sunday morning now unless the end is
I guess maybe in Hawaii. No, I guess it's only a little bit later in the East Coast
So what are we doing? Let me see. I hope I was hoping I'm another surprise ready for you
But I have to throw it together kind of now and
Do that bit and I'm in so behind on writing songs and stuff. I
I think there's a reality Nancy while she's like just setting her on or I think she's not good at the way they sound.
Reality Nancy, this one's for you.
Okay, well, I think I had a copy to make of it.
This might be the Karen song.
Okay, I'll have to find yours later Nancy, I don't see you.
I just remember your call.
She keep the phone, you'll be sorry.
Ah, there's your intro, in X.
Can you see me?
Oh, there I am.
Okay.
I see you, I see you now.
Oh, look at your text.
I just sent you pictures.
Oh, thank you so much.
Oh my gosh, I'm like now seeing all these kind of dogs
and I keep asking if every dog I see is a Peek-A-Neese.
Yeah.
They're like, no, this is like a Bichon Frees.
I was like, I'm just like Peek-A-Neese crazy.
But yeah, you know what happened today?
What happened?
Let's see.
I don't know, not too much. I mean, I didn't see very much happening anywhere, but
yeah, I think that if you need that brand new video, it's on my wall. That's the best place
to get it. You just have to scroll down a little bit. Good. I'm going to use that. He's crazy.
Look at my legs. We're elephantitis. I don't have diabetes. I don't have any. He doesn't
even know me, and he's messing with my friends. You know, messaging them.
It's terrible. He's a weirdo, but they all know about him.
the only thing that the only person that resembles an animal is him and it's he looks like that like that
art bark you know that weird art bark on children's television so i i mean it's like you know art
health you think it's art third the art of art i'm not sure but uh or he looks like spongebob
or like a spongebob character that's big yeah there's something wrong with him he has mental
issues and and i sent you his boss's email okay you can message him and he'll look at the time
During during work, and he lied saying my neighbor my neighbor. No, it's him
They know on the other day, and he was using a deep voice
But I and he come he came on his name was Daria of the 90s show
Oh all these crazy towns that he makes in the box. He has no not one single friend at all
And it's sad
Mean even the bots don't like him very much. I mean they come and say Q army, but then they ever ever see them turn on him before
I know right and it's just yeah, I don't know. I guess he's paced his little money for that
You know, he had even live in the park
I mean
Yeah, that's it. That's it. He has no life. No, we said he has a girlfriend. He's never with anybody. He's always alone and
He's a woman or Russian
Nobody in Russia and then he was saying he was homeless in a little clip the other day
No, he lives in that dump right there. He's been docks before and that's where he was
The oofy guy went over there. Yeah, that's how I got the information
Well, I think Oofy's a little bit iffy sometimes, but no, I'm just kidding. Yeah. Yeah, I guess he's just a sick guy, has no friends, nothing, no communication with the outside world.
I don't feel like he should go to like, you know, probably be arrested, but then he should be in the support group inside of the jail.
Yeah, and he has no friends at all, and he's reaching out to the people that we know, and they all know that he's sick. They send me his messages, and they just don't really interact with them.
if he goes to jail, he'll be in heaven.
Yeah, right?
And then there's Mike's shot
and it shows that he's five foot seven.
Oh my God.
Yeah, I got a snapshot of this shot.
You're five foot eight, right?
You're taller than him.
No, I'm five foot four.
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
I'm five foot four.
But if you like, you know,
you went out and met in women,
if you were to do the average,
you would be like five feet taller than him.
You know what?
I probably should have been,
You know
Yeah, see
Man
Yeah, and he's just a shorty. He's five seven and it showed it on on his that guy they posted his picture
Uh-huh
Who's that guy he was dating like 17 year old named Peter like why was he dating some 17 year old?
You know that story. I don't know anything about the uh-uh what happened. He was a guy with some guy running around outside
Then they started he started screaming got the street that he started terrorizing this poor Mexican lady that was
Her dog was working and that's the thing that doesn't make sense. He lies about everything. That's his only buddy, I guess
Okay, and he was trying to say that and I have that recorded. Oh, I sure do
Where he was telling me that that was actually Gamble's friend and Gamble set him up by send
Everybody and nobody even knows who to mostly people are so it's like yeah, that's it's just a liar
But that's what he was saying, you know, he just makes up
Next he's been calling us
I annexed that pedophiles on his on his thumbnails for days.
Who? Brandy Q.
That weirdo, that the big pit pedo.
How do you say weirdo?
Who gives a shit?
I know, right?
He's a sick, sick guy.
I don't even know him.
But look, did you see the picture?
Let's do it.
That's my legs.
Uh, now I know I sent it to show them or no, no, no, yeah, I guess you can you can show her rain not everybody on there
Just your summer show rain. I'll try to go back. Yeah. Yes. That's my love. Um, no, you can show ahead
So I think clumsy's mad at me. I don't know why
But um, yeah, I tried I tried going to a stream um like a few times and you wouldn't let me up
Everybody else up guys. She said it's not a joxie. I can share. I and X has lovely. Hey lovely tan legs
They're not elephants legs. They're lovely. Okay. Yeah, that's my legs now right now. That was my cat up there
Right up by my foot
Saying I have elephant titus because I have diabetes. I don't have no diabetes. I don't have anything
Yeah, those are my legs and those are my gray shorts that I got on Amazon. Oh
Yeah, they're comfortable too. Yeah, they're like bike shorts
Um, so I tried going to clumsy stream and he wouldn't let me up, but he let everybody else
So I tried going like because you he did you time them out the other night and then
I didn't time anybody out. Oh, no, no, you untimed him out
I didn't like he understands that you and you like coming up for 10 seconds. So he was because Arthur hit him
Right. Yeah, I defended clumsy, but I don't know why he'd be mad at me like
I tried going on his panel a few times and like you wouldn't let me up.
I want to try something different today. I get this book. It's a divination. It's called
Bibliomancy because when you just open the page to the book and I opened a page to a story today
it was it was just a random it was like it's so cool so I'm gonna open a page or random maybe
let's not give us the answer to the question. It's very short of those stories okay. Well maybe.
I want you can tell him you can tell him or is what she's trying to say
I wanted to yeah, like get your opinion and you know like
Let him know yourself psyche no go through a book or whatever just tell him hey
I think that you've misunderstood. She was trying to help you out or whatever
Um, well, I mean, like when you have the time, like it's not urgent, you know, anything
I think he usually comes here. I mean, it's like, I mean, I can leave, but then I don't let
If I leave and rain always, it's not tough. Can I just read the baby a spare story?
I just wanted to know, like, you know, what's up with that? You know, like, is he mad at me?
I think he might be a female to male transgender and so maybe it's just the time of the month
But like I didn't do anything to him, like I don't understand.
Okay, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've had my ups and downs with the clumsies, but you know, I, I'm an upswing, so you don't want to worry.
I'm just confused by it, is all.
Okay, so this is like, so this is like a cute, so this story, it's called the babyish bear.
Hold on, I'm gonna take down my background.
Can you just see this?
I just opened to this.
And so I just think of, you know, your baby cat.
I think of your baby cat a little bit.
Okay, so.
Well, when you have the time, psyche, I will tell him right after that, right after I showed you the story, it's only a short story.
There's a lady coming with her little, with her little, uh,
No, it's like light brown they'd get like of the Sun depending the sunlight and sit like my dad's hair
This lady is like this lady is a little older, but but it's like it's just
We're doing the two or something. They look like she's about 80 years old or something. Oh, it's Christine. Must be Christians, Christine
So it says when Jack was given a hug. It's sorry a big present for his birthday. He was impressed. It was from mrs.
merino
an elderly lady who lived nearby. Jack had never paid much attention to her before.
He thought she was slightly strange because she wore funny clothes
and talked to herself as she walked down the street. But a present was a presence,
so maybe Mrs. Moreno had hidden depths.
As soon as he had ripped off the paper, Jack changed his mind.
It was a bear, a great big fluffy teddy bear with a ribbon around his neck.
Even Jack's mother had a smile.
How lovely.
You must say thank you to Mrs. Marino when you see her.
Jack's mind was already on other problems.
The bear had to be hidden and fast.
His friends were coming to his party in a couple of hours and there was no way they
could see this bear.
If only it wasn't so enormous, you tried to hide it in the cupboards, you tried to push it under the bed,
you tried to stuff it into the bag where the dirty laundry was kept, but nothing worked.
The bear was there, it was too big to hide.
Jack tried placing it.
in various positions around his house.
Maybe it could just blend with the furniture somewhere.
But he found that whenever he went back into that room,
kind of pretending he didn't know there was a bear in there.
The first thing he could do was that silly, hello?
You like this?
It was a silly.
What caught his eye was a silly, fluffy face.
It was almost time for the party
when Jack had a brilliant idea.
If I hurry, I've got time to go thank Mrs. Marino,
he told his mother.
She was suspicious, of course, but she let him go.
He struggled down the street with the bear.
Mrs. Marino opened the door.
His words came out of it in a rush.
Mrs. Marino, thank you very much for my presence.
My party, my credit, my gift, damage.
So could you please keep them on for the afternoon, please?
Mrs. Marino, they're puzzled.
won't want a bear at your age, will you? Did you like the watch? Jack shook his head. The watch
that Mrs. Marino showed him the little opening in the bear's back where you could tuck things away,
and she gave him the most amazing watch that was inside and explained that she thought the bear
would stop it from getting squished or stood out among the presents. I was right, Jack told his
mother when he got home. She is strange, but she's okay too. More than okay. Oh look, it's time for my
And see if she was saying I didn't send you a bear. I sent you a watch. Oh see it and it all worked out. There was a watch inside of the bear.
Isn't that a great story? It's open to that random store. Is that crazy?
Saiki, how high are you right now?
I have the best vape, and I slept for like two days straight, and so...
Oh, shit.
Where is everyone? I don't know, but nobody wants to come here.
Seven people are being called.
I think people are scared all of a sudden.
All the drama that had been going on.
I didn't turn into it.
Well, also, people are on other panels, so...
I know, but, I mean, hello, and we have some love for Psyche.
I mean, I've been around for like...
Psyche, you know I always love you.
You will, like that. I like that.
Yeah, you'll always like me. Oh, I'll always love you. Oh, I'll always love you. I love you, too
psyche
I love I love everybody pookie pirates no offense. This is you going live not a show
Hey, you know what it is. It's whatever I wanted to be so if I call it a show
It's a show if I call it me streaming if I call myself a legend right I can call myself, you know
If you if he wants to be called the wizard, he can I
Can play with the languages and do anything I want black Tyler psyche looking like he's about to steal all
All of what can on those precious vibranium and then selling it to the highest bidder
Wakanda
It's a it's a fictional place like Nigeria, but they call it Wakanda
Okay, yeah, like, you know, I guess they're coming to the winter soldier the winter soldier look
Southwest when
When did you come out because I wasn't I wasn't excited to stream today at all until then my main channel
Yeah, and this person's like you banned him psyche. No, but I mean I'm just asking him who is he?
I don't I know he's I don't remember anybody doing I haven't received a basic donation
Except for a few few special angels like keeping me afloat, you know a few people but
Um, you know, most people, oh, Hebrew hammer.
Because Hebrew hammer called me a goyim, and I don't like the term goyim, and it was offensive.
What is that?
It means cattle.
It's like, but it's like a Jewish, Yiddish term for cattle.
Goyim?
I've never heard that.
Goyim, G-O-Y-I-M.
It's like, you know Hebrew?
Yeah.
Well, I mean it's like not perfectly, but I mean as I said y'all the alphabet of it and I can do I okay now
So he wasn't talking like hey, I'll unban you
And we always say that and then it's like well, who are you referring to when you said that and why do I look like Paul Bunyan to
I mean, it's like wow
a little bit I
Was thinking like a butch lesbian. I'm just kidding
He's a goyems, but we have some of this going himself like oh people food. Well, what do you like to eat like?
I mean people food, that means like what people eat,
like I know people eat animals and stuff,
but we need plants and we need like a people food.
Go ahead and stop.
Like what's like real food, like.
Come
You know Kate and I reconciled I think I maybe maybe I can smooth things over a little bit for you
See, that's what I like about you psyche. You're so understanding
Yeah, I went to her show and I said I said I
She told me one of the first people she said don't have Brandon. She's like red alert red alert
Yeah, that was an issue at first and now now she's listening to this nut
I didn't know that she was so two-faced and starting a bunch of shit behind the scenes and she has been she's just been trying
To hate bond against Barb and beta
I'll tell you about that later, but I'm not mentioning her right now because I've busted her and I'm just so sick of it
You know the people being so two-faced and thank you Barry the turtle for showing me what a liar
She is and showing me proof
You should start out you should start to do it do a stream called busting Barb and then do one called busting Vita
I don't know. I think it's probably the one busting Nancy because she was the one that was ostracized from the whole group went when
Abba
things here you can bust everyone
Yeah, I mean what you remember Abba she used to be Aaron Carter's girlfriend for a while and then she had her own group or whatever the
oranges
Okay, well her she kicked out Nancy for a reason because Nancy was shady and then Nancy docks Barb's son
And did a horrible thing to all these people and then she complained about how they turned on her and I fell for her bullshit
I thought she was sweet and stuff, you know
Cuz she came to me asking me for help because Gamble went at her on his live one night and
Humiliated her and she was sending people to me saying do you know I annex?
If she blocked me, can you ask her to unblock me?
And she was just trying to hate Bonn,
and I didn't know this woman then.
But boy, did I find out what a two-faced person she is,
and Mary showed me that,
because she's been going between Kate and Nancy.
You know, she's been talking to Nancy was just doing that to get get at beta
Because she she was more worried about her name being said, but she's a coward because she won't join panels
Yeah, I figured out why my number was so low
It's like because somebody hit everybody at a road mod and they hit everybody today
Today who did you mod?
Don't know I mean there's people like that. I mean there's like I'm so I have to I'm unmodding everybody right now
And I'll slowly like mod you back if I like just like well, it wasn't me
Okay, I don't ban people for no reason
I didn't even know you unmodded us
No, I didn't, I didn't, I canceled it, I canceled it, should I?
Yeah, no.
You should unmod, you should unmod.
I didn't unmod anybody, I'm unhiding everybody.
They didn't show you who did it, didn't it?
Show you who it's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's
the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's
Sorry people they probably and I say people get so mad when they come in and it's like they're not
They're not uh, they're not modded sometimes to get offended
But I mean I did when that happened to me look they hit everybody did everybody that wasn't a mod
They got hit in every single person. So I really do have to um
Take down. I mean, I'll leave you up to a grateful. I'll leave a certain few people up there. Yeah in range
I'm a good mod. Yeah, reality Nancy. I don't ban people. I
Might time them out, but you know
I mean, but when I time out, it's not for long either.
Guys, if a mod comes across any of the shows
that you can, somebody know.
Like five minutes at most.
Oh yeah, grateful.
You're here and you're here.
Oh my God.
I'm doing this.
I'm doing the mod.
What happened?
I was deleting all the mod.
I have like a over 100 moderators, oh my God.
I'm discarding the changes again.
Did you mod that Vita?
Didn't I heard something about that you modded her the other day?
I was trying, like, you know, she was gonna hit it and then she would say,
she would, then she would like ban me from her chat and stuff.
And I wasn't, it was just a mod, it's a mod like leaving her comment.
And I think I'll just, I'll just mod you just so you don't get hit in.
You know, just as a courtesy to her.
And then, uh, and then she like, was like, kept lying and saying,
like making accusations towards me.
Okay, now I'm going to the hidden people hidden users. Okay, so that how many people are hidden? Oh my god
There's like 200 people hidden
Yeah, everybody everybody was hidden and it's like and then I have to click each person
And then I have to like let a bunch of trolls back to just be fair. I mean, were you were you live earlier?
I was live yesterday or was I not even yesterday not even for very long yesterday just like that last night a little bit
Yeah, holding my cock. I have to let back I am a tail. Oh my god
I can't believe but then I love a lot of these people that hold in person really didn't like me
Oh, I bet that sounds familiar someday a block. I don't know. I don't think this is real name
It sounds like a joke to me. Well, he he really doesn't like me for some reason
How could anybody that knows you not like you?
Exactly, like they don't know me.
They're troll and they're unhappy.
I know they just like live under like a bridge and they need to
They heard of Rita before and they were using her picture, the ugly picture
Oh my god, you know, I remember that hilarious thing, I'm not gonna play it again, but I remember
when I played that thing where I played Trinity Sweet Pea on Good Times show
She wrote me a message and she's like, I am a disgusting piece of human garbage
and that she said nobody laughs
With me everyone just laughs at me, and I'm not entertaining at all. And then she said good times
Psyche you've been pretending to meet me on your panel yesterday, and you look like a fool
And then she goes at Alexandra. Oh, and here go look at the clip for how
He talked using my voice and stuff like that. I mean, it's like
Beta sweet pea sweet pea
Yeah. Oh, okay. Yeah, I don't know who Sweet Pea is.
Well, you're lucky because she's a terrible, terrible person.
Mm-hmm. I don't know who that person is either.
She's awful. She's really, really annoying. She's like a two-phase. She's like a...
That's almost everybody on there.
Yeah, she had a channel that was all me. Her channel was all like 100% me.
And I wasn't even that... I wasn't really funny on the channel too.
You know, there was just all me though, you know whole thing. So oh my god. I was okay. So I'm so sorry for people that were hidden
I'm gonna have to put a note
Well, maybe they're hidden for a reason. I wouldn't be too worried about it right now because look at what happens. You
Hundreds of people are missing my hidden users. Oh my god
Yeah, hundreds of people. Okay. No, I'm almost done almost done. But Joe Shippley was hidden brand. Oh my god
Joe Shippley was hidden to him. It's me. Joe's annoying
I don't like him drunk all the time. He's drunk most of the time and he's just really irritating and breathing
There's somebody named nerdy nerdy digger
Okay, I'm I'm unbanning everybody just for well. Yeah, I'd be careful because that's probably one of
Brandon's bought accounts that you're unbanning. I know I'm coming with all of them again
We're a burst burst in a laugh and and and and dismantle them for parts on his robots
I'll get out your screwdrivers and wrenches everybody. That's what they're for
Yeah, he's just a weirdo man doesn't shut up man
He has no life no friends
And he only has that one guy that you saw the video and he would even claim him as a friend
Because he was there recording him when he was attacking the dog and that old lady
And when the police asked them they said well, who are you to him because you're hanging out here and videotaping it and
He's are you his friend and he said no? He said I'm an acquaintance
He would even claim him yeah
Yeah, well, it's like yeah, yeah, I mean he seems to know pretty well they're talking about
Yeah, you know because he was talking to him and then I saw another clip where there were he acted like he wanted to grape that guy
I know nuts and going crazy. Yeah, I think it was a clip you showed
Remember that guy was like no no like it like he was really wanting to do something to him
Right
is in the fanboys and trannies he said. Yeah see yeah oh that's right he did he say that one
time he was in with something that was a different both sexes or something. Yeah that's what he said
that he's so weird and he lies about Ganville and everybody else being this and that and it's no
Now we got the weirdos coming out of the woodworks.
Okay, everyone's getting unbanned.
Can I spread the word that everyone got hidden by a rogue mod?
And I'm sorry about that.
Like, I have to un-mod maybe somebody.
At least the word Jordana was hidden.
Oh my god.
She was getting to you had her um, you know
Weird I thought she would show you especially who's who's uh banning them because I remember
Many that's moderate can go to old episode and then they can go into the chat and then they can just go through the chat
I had hide every that was there. Oh, and they can just go find a bunch of episodes like that
But it's a kind of dedicated how many they did
Oh my god, they hit a lot of friends of mine.
I mean, it's like I hate when they do this.
Well, yeah, just be careful who you mod.
You're just modding too many people right now.
Yeah.
Oh, look at Lola in the background.
Love to look at Lola.
OK, I just.
Fast fall.
Yeah.
And oh, look at Lola.
I was right here too.
Lenore.
Oh, they're fast asleep.
Yeah, did she always sleep in like flat surfaces?
Um, she wants to she likes to sleep. I'm like, you know, she likes to sleep in those books for right now. I don't know. Um,
it's
Um,
Monarch crash too right here, but the two babies are right here. Oh
by me
Yeah, the two youngest ones are they sleeping together now though, but they're not playing together yet
So hopefully the youngest one will start playing with her
Yeah, I mean, it's like I think that they will get used to each other. I think so. Yeah
Now they're at least closer to each other to sleep like practically together, but they're not hanging out yet
Because the new one is kind of like, you know, just I mean he was it was a feral baby cat
So she's getting you she likes being inside and happy, you know, but as far as toy is she's kind of confused as to what they are
Yeah, well, I mean it's like they are I mean cats are very smart. They will probably pick up on it
I mean, it's a basically stuff stuff move around and stuff. And I think it's
Like he's like he's somebody's backstage. Oh, somebody's backstage. Okay, let's be careful. I will
Let's see. Can you guys if it's somebody can you probably Brandon and their name is oh my god
It's like it's no it says okay. His name is his name is your your rez
Or as 747 I'll put the banner up the 47 you're as 47
Yeah, you guys it's me. It's you're as 47. I'm from mr. Extendo's channel
Somebody knows
Yeah, I know you. Thank you. Oh, I'm sorry. Hey, I get four months all day. I did it. It was a little bit different.
Thanks, man. I'm glad you're here.
Yeah, you guys. Don't mind me. I'm just hanging out with my people. I'm having some beers. That's all.
I was on like, I was on, I was on TikTok recently and there's really, really, really cool stuff.
You gotta go and buy the chew with us right now. I know it's really dark where I'm sitting at, but like, here's my flashlight.
Oh, I love the flashlight. Oh, it's like that. It's like a UFO.
No, no, it's not kind of flashlight. It's flashlight.
Oh, it's not a flashlight? Oh my God.
Oh, crap. Oh, yeah, there is a light out here. Now you guys can see me. Awesome. Are you? Hi. Okay. You're somebody else I know, right? I know you write it in a name. Oh, the light went out. The light went out. Yeah, the W-H-I-T.
But he's trying to fix it. He's trying to fix the lighting. Um, okay. I'm trying to you guys
Is everyone getting it unbanned? I mean, I say I try to unbanned every single person
Psyche, how's it going man? I noticed you got a haircut. Yeah, I got a haircut
I feel like I feel like a new man really it's like it's really like just
Kind of like what you look like a haircut man. The long the long caro didn't really suit you
No, it's like, I mean, I just like, I mean, I look back on it, I looked kind of like, yeah, kind of weird, and I was like, always happy, I was like, oh, look how I can grow my hair long in Jesus, but it's like, I just, like Jesus Christ, like, that's one of the best things, so.
Okay, ghost was hidden, beauty, Q was hidden.
Ghost was hidden? Oh, no.
Yep, yep, Rando was hidden. Okay, everyone was, everyone was unhidden. I just unhidden like 200 people.
Yeah, man, and you didn't even know. Yeah, careful who you mod
Say psyche your your haircut makes you look 10 years younger. Yeah, you do look way younger. You look great
Back to I'm just like back and so you can see my I don't really I'm not really balding. It's like no, not at all
Is this is like natural
my the shape of our
I always used to say it's where my horns used to be or something like that.
Horns.
Ugh, my stalker's here, Patrick New York.
He stalks me.
Hey, White Dog, is that, so that White...
Okay, so White Dog is different than Europe.
White Dog.
Yeah, that's...
Psyche, that Patrick New York guy, he stalks me everywhere.
Yeah, he stalking Rain, then I have to stop stalking him.
He's obsessed.
Wait, he's in the chat?
Yeah, the one putting your picture up it's only came up with your name and they had a picture of your eyes
I don't know who was this they just used your name. It's a rain. And then it's gay tea gay tea
I know he's just saying that
No, no, no, they really there's one game gay tea and it was they don't got my picture
Well, it was just a picture. I just thought go I look like Daria's
Where did these weirdos get these pictures for shit like what the fuck
I'm sorry, look at, he's calling you pathetic or anything.
She's not pathetic, Patrick, you know what I'm saying.
Patrick, you don't even go on panel, you weirdo.
Yeah, I hear you, man.
So, you guys, how's it going, man?
How's it going?
I mean, I smacked, I mean, I smacked.
How are you?
Mr. Accendo back from Europe right now,
I did, I did, I did, I did, I did, I did.
Mr. Accendo is back, and also hello.
But yeah, Mr. Accendo is back.
Yes, okay, good. No, so you don't mod that person there. That's a fake JT. That's not the real JT
It's a fake it's a fake JT
Understand what that means
Well, okay, but okay, I went on a show yesterday called good times for life
And I pretended to be a woman named sweepie and I was on him for at least an hour talking about the most disgusting shit
And I and he never figured out that I wasn't a woman named sweepie like he and he knows me
And it's like I just like this I barely discussed my voice and then so sweepie tagged me in a postage
She said she's had a miscarriage of the earth basically and then I'm not funny. I'm not entertaining
And everyone just laughs at me, not with me.
And then she said that, good times,
please, you're making a fool out of yourself,
believing that she was me.
It wasn't me that she has to explain it so far.
Oh, White Dog.
White Dog, what's up, man?
I remember you.
Yeah, I don't have to have to remod white thought I have to remod some people so they get protected
You know you shouldn't get rid of all you shouldn't time out people from
From chat or whatever because they even trolls they help out with the but they help out with the channel
You know that yeah, that's true. Sometimes. I mean, it's just like there's just like some comments
And I really haven't wanted to see yeah, the rude ones are especially like that Brandon guy that makes a million account
The algorithm, I guess, I'm not sure, but.
Oh, was that you who was speaking on, uh, inks?
Yeah, I and X. Yeah.
Wait, are you inks, Capelli?
Is that you or are you?
Is that different?
Are you? Is your name something else?
No, something else.
All the matter, too.
Oh, OK, because I thought if you're in
Capelli, that you'd be one of my mods, basically.
Yeah, no. Make up your minds.
Am I 300 pounds or am I?
Do I look like a little boy?
Make up your minds.
Weirdos, yeah, no, right
Oh by the way, I don't know am I yeah, you look skinny. I don't know am I fat
Yeah, that's what I was asking. Are you guys fat or something?
Yeah, is that it right?
Look fat to you. Oh, no your profile picture looks like awesome
What the hell is the other profile picture? I don't know what the hell that is, but it's a picture
You just showed my legs are earlier on the stream. I just took a picture
Yeah, that I got elephant Titus when he made an old picture mine way bigger than I was
Yeah elephant Titus that I have diabetes and I have blood fresh I don't have any of that man, you know, I'm thin
The elephant Titus he says because he made that picture. He made that a I picture even more so a I made it blew it up
You know and saying that I did is yeah
Because he made it even bigger than it was
Yeah, he was weird
What's the guy's name? What's the guy's rocky dentistry there? There's a rocky dentistry, but he's like happy to
Like he you have another person backstage. Okay. I'm so sorry
Be careful. You'll get stuck on your finger by the way. Is that how far it goes? Oh
Oh my god
I banned this person from the show though, I mean and then she said she doesn't like me
I'll read all we have to read the message and then I'll let her on
It's a promise you want more mom, but I'll have to read the message
Listen to this message that I received from this person. I'm gonna find it
So it says
No, yeah good man, I'll be
Sitting here do my own thing
Um, I mean, he's, I mean, it's, I mean, there's so many, wait, wait, did you, did you complain?
Oh, the dab?
Okay.
No, no.
So here's our conversation.
Young Psyche.
What are you guys talking about anyways, man?
This woman know well who you brought to meet.
But listen, but here's what happened.
Um, she poor mom meet for like the fourth time or fifth time.
And I said,
Why does she do that?
i don't know but i said you promise i'm disappointed in you she said why and she said why and i said
you flashed and she goes oh really and i said are you talking about psyche i mean noel i'm
psyche i mean were you talking about flurry diamond no flurry diamond is not seven she looks like
And I said, I'll provide her again.
I said, you promised you wouldn't.
And she goes, who care?
I said, I can lose my channel, I care.
She goes, who's care?
You're banned, don't come back.
And she said, shut up.
And I said, no, I'm so disappointed in you.
She says, I do not like you.
I said, good, stay away, you promise breaker.
And guess who's here tonight?
Is there a brother flashlight mold on there?
Hi, very normal.
Hey, mom, how are you, mommy?
I'm doing great. Are you I want I will I will I will behave when she's on
Okay, no, I'll behave
Mommy, how are you?
You'll know you look like I'm one of those like you know those like I'm
Those trolls like they have like crazy hair, but like some of them don't have me. Oh
I was just saying hello. How's it going?
Good. How are you and who and who are you? Oh, I'm your res 47
Hey
Mr. Extendo's show I were in his discord and we were just joking around
Stop harassing people and on the side of me
Anybody in there like yes, you are so I'm asking to come to our house and stuff. I'm like, I'm not asking to go
I have it. I just played along with it
But um
Basically, I'm a mr. Extendo fan and the you're a 47 fan. Yeah. Well, I mean, I'm a mystery extender
We're like two and a half years. Oh
Please stop calling me mommy. No, I'm calling her
I'm the mommy and daddy of the show, Noelle, do you know that?
Why would you call me there, why would you text me there, I'm mad at you now.
I will behave, I will behave, I will behave.
And I want to ask you why did you break your promise when you were going to form up?
I can do whatever I want. So yeah, you can. You guys want to check out some expensive rings. I have right now. What's up, right here's one. I want to be next to you, Mommy.
See you guys. This is a wolf look at that. It's like oh, it's a ring
That's a ring. Oh
Right here you guys you guys see it
Yeah, yeah, I'm not her mommy
This is like
My ring. It's um
They seen that one like a lion face is that what it is so cute boy. You guys know opal
No, I'll do you like your ass you guys here's here's the army
No, do you like do you like your res it needs?
It needs the guy above you
You think he's cute yes, I think he's psyche. Do you see that everyone else too in the in the call? Do you guys see this?
Yeah, you're as no, I'll do your ass. Yes, and how old are you?
Yeah, no one's gonna be your daddy and just need to be your mom
How old are you?
That's that's $30,000. He's talking to you yours. How old are you yours? Oh, I'm 21 you guys
I'm 26, so can we be a friend on on on here
I know run into him then maybe but it's like yeah, I don't think he is I don't think he's
What's up? Mommy. I want to his, I want his uh YouTube channel. Mommy. Give it up for it.
He'll give it to you. Rez, what's your channel? You Rez, what's your channel? And you can
subscribe to mine. All your mums.
I'm not sure you're right
Well actually it has she has a
Sorry, I was just gonna have a wheelchair. I don't have a wheelchair. No, I want your
No, I want your channel. You're as yes. I yes, they do you you ask
Are you in the wheelchair?
No, I'm not
Look at those rings
What's your channel, dude?
Here's about your rings your rings. She wants your channel link. Be nice. Be nice
suck
Your wings suck
I mean, I can't control what you guys say.
Yo, where did everyone go?
I saw everyone left.
No, what's your channel?
What's your channel?
Yes, I do.
We're Psyche.
Psyche's up there on the corner on the top.
He's putting you guys together.
There's a love match.
A love match.
You and Noel.
I'm sitting on the corner.
Flirty Diamond was just here working.
Did they hurt you?
No, no, Joe, they're getting together.
Okay, well, so what the fuck are you guys trying to ask me earlier you guys were talking to me earlier?
She wants your channel
It's basically the same thing your res 47 you res 47. I'm just searched for that you are easy for seven
And you spell that no, well, or is that a little too many words basically yeah, and you please go to my channel
Well, you don't have to perfect friends are being made new subscribers are being made
That's why it's in my channel, dude. You are
47 look for you. You are
I only joined because Psyche told me, if you want to do my channel.
INX, are you going to interview INX, can you ask a few questions to the guest?
Because I would look to your style.
Okay.
I don't know.
I'm not an interviewer though.
I think Ray would be good interviewing.
Okay.
Anyways.
Do I interview?
Yeah.
He's asking.
Sorry.
He's doing something but who do you want me to interview them you can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them. You can interview them.
Um Canadian brother Raiden Boris everyone. Um Joe psyche has a cool haircut. Awesome. Okay. I was just reading some chats
So wait, what was your guys's question?
Where are you from? I'm from Canada, Ontario. Oh
Yeah, and what do you like to do? I am from Oh, what hi? Oh, hi. Oh, hi, yo
Oh
Yes, will you? Okay. I thought it was a long name. I did that. I guess Ohio is just
creation. That's like he's from waiter. I'm from California. Oh
That's cool. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Los Angeles and so yeah
You're a famous person basically after some Mars. Hey, I made for Mars. Oh my gosh
It's the Hebrew hammer coming up. Let me just put up the banner. Okay. No, I can trust
Are you girls from well, what's up, Hebrew? How are you?
Can you not hear
No, we can hear
Take off the sun like it's dark time you don't
Now you could keep them on
Okay, well, I bet you're lucky at your rest because sometimes I get my speedos here, but they're so dirty right now
So you're in love
They're dirty. Yeah, they're dirty. They're on the floor. Look at
They're sitting on my teeth, they're sitting right on the fucking
It's so strong
I didn't hear what you said to me, man
What I just said to you, uh, okay, so I make music and uh
So, I didn't show you my new videos, I just wanted to be clear about this, let me play it.
Come on.
Wait, I'm playing it now.
Hi, kiddies.
Because everyone's gonna get to recognize you'll see Samman makes a camera.
You're here in London.
You're like Adam 22, bro.
I like Adam 22.
That's Samman or Sam.
Who the fuck is this thing?
That would only be Samman if he got plastic surgery.
Yeah, why are you in that distance, girl?
Are you hurrying?
What is this ability?
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
I don't know, I don't know
I don't know
For me on the mirror, fear is in brah
Oh, we get voice answered in the night
There is a little heart in the sky
Lucky that I feel it, dude
I like it
I guess I do. This song actually slaps Psyche.
Thank you. Thank you.
Psyche, can you play a song?
Can you play a song that I can request from?
Mommy.
Can I request this? It's called My Mistake.
Ah, fuck, my phone's dying.
Fuck, thanks.
Damn it.
I'll play it out of my way out of the show.
Can I request a song, Psyche?
I'm not talking to you, guys.
I'm talking to Psyche.
I
Been the chat friend and I'll get so I'll play Joe you're bald bitch. Okay. I'll type it in the chat
Are you fighting you guys are all fighting now
JT already proved you're bald
Hey, be nice you guys be nice
No, that Joe shape Lee guys weird
Oh, okay
Yeah, he's shaped like a fucking pear, okay, I sent it I sent it on
Yeah, I played Violet Lonnie yeah, you should see it there
For all of the ladies and for all of the lonely men out there
Am I allowed to? Okay, so this is for all of them, but I'm just gonna post it in the chat and then they can
Visit it on their own time. I
Unless I'm getting a donation. I really don't want to play music right now. So I'm gonna
No, play it play it anyways. You don't have to make money off of it. Just play it for free do it for the fans
i know what i've been i've been i've been demon i said you care about making money i've been
demonized for a month but hey hey you know i'll play i'll play any song hey i don't i'll play i'll
play you a song hold on i'll play you a song
I mean, I don't know because listen to these small streamers. They're the problem because if someone like Violet Lonnie
Who is like 20s 20 subscribers like she'll sue me about about this because she has like
You're just not gonna do that to you man. It's not gonna do that
Be doing her favor plus
like it's not like yeah she does have a Spotify song but it shouldn't harm your
channel but i'm just saying like smaller because i just got i just got a strike from this um
someone that used the has been hotel music nah she's she's not
No, I'm just like I'll say I'm just post I post the name of the thing in the chat
I work and take it out if they want to just promote the band
I just can't play it on my show, but I mean if you would if you donate I'll do it
But it's like I'm just like I just don't want to take the risk right now
Even though you're a cool guy. I appreciate you being on the panel. I have my own like I'm getting
I'm like ready about to be re-monetized. So
Joe you smell like meth bitch psyche
Yes. Yes. No, well that's your cat
in the background.
There's Lenore and there is Lola.
So cute.
So cute there.
Yeah.
I have this really cool book on the 11th hour.
I don't know. It is kind of like, you know,
big for all ages. I guess it's like a mystery.
It's kind of elephant.
That's cool.
Yeah, it has like really cool drawings
and it's like a mystery.
But I like when I read that, do you like that story I read earlier, Noelle?
I can just open that.
That story was really good.
I just opened a page of the book, and so this is one for Noelle.
Here's the story for Noelle, okay, ready?
Noelle, this is called Bertram's Books, okay?
It's about a bear, okay?
It says, one day Bertram Bear.
announced he was going to have a grand clear out of his house.
I got far too much rubbish collected over the years.
He said, there's hardly room for me in my house.
Never mind anyone else.
And he smiled at Blarney's or Barney's granny.
Can I help you?
As Barney, I'm really good at clearing things out, aren't I, Dad?
Last time I'd let you help my clear out, not clear out my shit, I'd say this father.
I couldn't find anything for weeks, but if Bertram is willing to take the risk, that's his business.
Oh, I think we can find something for a small bear to do, said Bertram kindly.
When Barney and Granny arrived at Bertram's house,
we soon realized how big of a problem it was.
It looked as though it never got through anything
that way in his life.
There were newspapers in boxes.
Oh no, this is like my house.
Everywhere, most of them are books on every table
of chairs, pile them all over the floor.
That's my house, oh no.
So it says, I can't resist buying them to Bertram.
I just love books you see.
I quite understand.
but why not donate them to the library after you've read them, suggested Granny?
I'm sure Mr. Leaf would be very grateful. How clever you are, my dear, as always,
said Bertrand. All afternoon, the bears carried books out to the front of the house so the library
van could pick them up later. As Bertrand and Granny sat down for a rest, they looked around
for Barney. The little bear was nowhere to be seen. After two hours of frantic searching,
Randy was very worried indeed, but just then a van arrived from our library.
Has anyone lost a small bear? Asked the driver. This is some books with huge pile.
There was Barney, who was a lot like Winnie the Pooh,
hidden in a little house with books and enjoying an exciting story book as much as
he hadn't even noticed that he'd been walled in with books.
I've heard of bookworms
but it looks as though you and
I are both book bears, young Barney.
What do you think?
Patrick, Patrick, you're old and smelly bitch
and bald.
Can you please check my phone number?
Patrick's just mad because he's bound to a wheelchair
Yeah, he's just fucking, you know, he's a fucking weird
Oh, no, that's all the nor how cute and Joe's just mad because he's bald
He has this that fucking meth-headed bitch next to him
Oh, he was like, oh, what are you doing?
And he's like, oh, we're trying to get to your house.
I'm like, no, I mean, that was a joke on the show.
I see if you come anywhere near my house,
I'm going to be calling the police.
So, Joe?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, Joe.
I'm talking about Chris K.
Joe.
He's such a creeper.
He said he was going to bring that lady over here.
And I was just kidding.
You were kidding?
So you weren't really inviting him over?
Oh, I thought you were serious.
That Alexander woman said 85% off and stuff like that.
Psyche, Chris Kate thought you were serious.
Yeah, I thought we all thought you were serious.
This will be called, and there'll be a restraining order.
It's a restraining order.
I am but I said if I played with his butt, I'm not gonna be in yours, but I thought you were serious too
I thought you really wanted him to come over there and you know had a conversation like it was real
You got to be careful what you say on the internet man because he'll probably be at your door tomorrow
Um, Chris K
Psyche Psyche, you shouldn't even mod Patrick, New York. He's a weirdo. I thought I would just protect him and then he would like help me
No, you know what he does like he was bragging about having a wrench in every fucking panel
Well, you let him brag, but maybe he'll be proud of it and then he'll be befriending my child.
He's a weirdo. Look at the way he's talking about me.
What did he say? He said, oh, I'm being brainless, Joe.
He's obsessed. He's a stalker.
The little boy reign blocks channeled because he doesn't like me.
And then Patrick lapsed and reigned and he cries.
You're yeah, he's crying because he's over here fucking being pathetic and shit
Well, like I don't even pay attention to the weirdo and he has every little thing to say about me
Insane here, I mean it's just like
They haven't so mind-fucked. I might as well, you know mad cuz he's bald and old
It's just it's just a suggestion, you know
17 watching okay, so Noel
Why do you have that frown on your face and you you look like you're you're bringing the whole vibe
He's mad at somebody
She's she's mad at Patrick for being a creep
Who's Tyler he said that you called them a bitch
Psyche, who is that Psyche?
He probably didn't know.
Psyche, who is that?
who's Tyler is that goes wait a minute that could be ghost you said you had him hidden by accident
I had everybody so everyone's back in the chat oh okay I feel like I feel like it's been a horror
movie everyone starts it would disappear well come come he'll be in and an account under the name
Tyler remember he did that twice before he's a mod why aren't you even looking out
What do you wait in there? He's modding still right now. Is that that name that's a teller?
He's just whining in the chat
Yeah, teller did that join
Yeah, join your pussy
Join panel. He's always whining
Bitch, it's like he said that in real bitchy tone
Damn, okay, who's this black Tyler nobody's obsessing on you you stalked me Patrick
Weirdo
You followed me all the way here, bitch
Okay, I put this I look in the link
So oh
I was gonna fit like Christine
Oh, what she's on with her show is never okay. It was really embarrassing because she
Because so ever everyone shared her show with me like oh here's Christine show and I was I assumed like she had a new show
Summer doing
It's almost fall
She's doing okay
Yeah, she's doing good. Okay. She's been going at beta lately. Yeah, why?
Because we are in some piece of shit and then the liar
Wow, look at these grown-ass men bullying a 27 year old woman
Get a life
It is not. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, all these are going no, well
Yes, I am a 26. Yes. Yes, they are. I was talking about me. I'm 27. I'm
20 us
I'm 26. Don't you have a gun?
Somebody's bullying you and chat. Are you okay rain?
Are you okay? Yeah, I can handle these bald weirdos. Yeah, I just ignore them or your mod is killed delete it delete the stupid
Well, I can't do anything because they're modded
Oh, they're my
He had modded that trick if that's him doing it
He's doing it. So who's gonna be in chat? Get ready bitch
You're about to get timed out bitch
Wow, so you guys like that
Rain. Oh, I love the music video. Yes. No rain. Um, are you okay? Yeah, I'm okay. Are you okay?
Yes, of course, I am
Here yeah, rain are we okay together?
Yeah, we're okay
I'll play a sing song maybe. I'll play the Joe Shippley song, the Joe Shippley song.
Oh gosh. Oh my god, never, what is the song about?
It's a song about... Oh, oh ghost is here, we'll wait on it.
Okay. Ghost is on here. Oh gosh. Oh gosh, that ghost. Oh gosh.
My god. He's a creep. Yes, yes.
That's a song, he's waiting for a song. Why is he quiet? Why is he crying? Yeah.
Cuz he's waiting for a song
Why are you crying?
He's a dumb ghost
Maricorki from life goes on
Okay, I'm sharing
Okay, I'll see you ready for your song. Here it comes
Here it comes. Go see
You're ready
Can you nap on him? Oh my god, that's wrong. I can't he's
Oh my god, I'm so sorry. Can you nap on him? Okay. No
Yeah, he's back
Yeah, you guys my phone died my phone died
I got brought back to life. Yes
John Wick let's go John Wick
That goes through the night
That's how you know
The haunts alive
Lights flicker
Chats in the right
And somewhere goes
About to die
Like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks
Cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling
The trolls start crying
Ghosts just grins
Let's fucking go chaos
What the hell
Like true
Help me down
When the sky lost its hue
They can't see the light when my storm
But I remember I was reborn
May I have permission to crash out?
Coastal Reddy did it to throw the stakes
That's his war cry sound
Every hate again when the chat brings it loud
It's closed over baby
Psyche is proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
They talk slick
Why is he still around?
For kindness is rare on this battle
We still chose to believe
Thank you
When most just lie
And chose to leave me
Also, um
Thank you
Crash it out
In a world full of clowns
He's the last to fake
Screen went dark
Kept me awake all the noise
F-
Turnin' pain into digital flame. May I have permission to crash out?
You were ready, ghost run. You were ready, ghost run.
You were ready, ghost run.
Here comes the dream. Dumb dumb to the ones who doubt the reason the flame.
Pass the ghost on.
I'm sorry. She liked you.
That is good.
That was good. That was so good. Did she see? Did she see? Did she see me? Oh, right. Did she see me?
Yeah, I saw you. Oh my god. Everybody was dancing.
We're gonna see you. Uh, psyche. Yo, I, I sent it right, right there in the chat. You should see it.
I should say Violet Lonnie. Um, play her song. You're not, nothing's gonna happen anyways.
I'm not scared. Hey, are you heard of that song Eminem? I'm not afraid
Yeah, I heard of that song, but don't play that play by Lonnie. My I was like he's not afraid of shit
I'm not because I lost my fear of my fear reflex
Move psyche. I'm not even trying to be an asshole. I'm just asking if you could play it
All right, awesome. Awesome, man. Okay. Are you reading me if I've no donation, please?
Yeah, man, I'll fucking do it to you if you play it. Okay, I'm playing it. I
Can't hear it. If you drive a hard bargain, but I like it. I like you. Please. It's beautiful
Okay, Violet and mom can you text me?
I like your turning violent violent violent. Why did I keep this saying that? Violet Lonnie my mistake. I don't see it
No, I see my I don't see that song. Yeah, I see. Oh, I hear this
Okay, I have
You know my mistake. I want to want to want to know my way. Oh
Oh my mistake, you know, that's how it goes. I get a strike
No, you're not gonna get a strike. No, you're not because she's she's only like from YouTube
No, she's not underage
Oh my god, I tried to match it here and it didn't work.
Okay, anyways.
It's pretty hard, why is it still loud?
Just play it.
What's up?
Okay, anyways.
Stay.
Oh my god, just play it.
Give me things at once.
Okay, I'm gonna play the whole wall.
Just play it.
What's up?
Oh my god, I like it.
It's like me.
I
It's not gonna harm your channel I wouldn't I would not do that to you man
Who is the welcome I wouldn't do that to you
Fuck you, I'm not I'm not undercover
I think we're in my black or what?
We're under cover alcoholic.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay, thank you, you're playing here.
Everyone listen to this song.
Thank you, thank you.
Not gonna make you mine next this game
I'm gonna catch your eye and then look away
You'll flip my hair and pray
You'll notice somewhere I don't dare my way
I know I'm gonna make you mine
I think I better leave it be this time then
I'm walking your way, you ask my name
Oops, I'm safe
i'm breaking my rules to the highest level y'all i can think about is how you look good with me
i'm feeling like i'm gonna make you next skate i'm gonna get your eye and then look away i'll flip
Calling your name, oops, my mistake
Got the chase from my whole world away
Ok, I ended this because I just wanted to get a picture and she looks like she's 13 years old.
I just don't want to play like a kid to become my child.
She's not a kid, psych.
I know.
No, she's young.
I don't...
She has one of those young faces there.
I know.
I mean, that's what my sister looks like in pictures.
Like, if you go to one of her videos of her recent lives, like, you'll see she's not a fucking kid, man.
Alright, well...
I just, that was good though, I liked what I've made in a minute, I mean, it's like-
Did you like it?
You would definitely be checking her channel out then, man.
She's awesome.
Like, join her lives once in a while.
She goes live every day for one hour.
But like, at random times.
There is, like, um, I do like this group, um,
the guy who I like the most.
Wayne!
Did you like that song?
Um, uh, no?
No, I do not.
Okay, well, I mean it's everyone has different taste
Yo, if you're gonna play a Christmas song if you're gonna play Christmas song play I'm a
Grandma got ran over by a reindeer
You actually have that song? You actually have that song?
I made a version about Christine. I've actually made two versions about Christine with it.
Grandma got ran over by a reindeer
Walking home from my house Christmas Eve
You can even say that it was Santa
But that's for me and grandpa, you believe?
Yeah, we know the word.
Forgetting the goals after that
Yeah, true true
I didn't talk to them, I talked to them for a minute.
So I just sit out here, I sit out here, but eventually I'll head back.
I'll probably go to Desmond's after this.
No, don't, I don't really, I want you to do a new piano.
Yeah, at least so.
I should move in with me.
We'll just sit inside.
What do I do with your chord when I'm done with this?
Do I just leave it?
Just unplug the fucking thing.
Should I just leave it by your um...
Just unplug whatever.
I'm gonna go grab another beer anyway because I'm done.
Okay, grab it.
I already done shit already.
Okay, well, I'll play the Arthur song.
Do you want to hear the Arthur song no well?
Yeah, go ahead.
Play it, play it, bro.
Okay, here you go.
Sorry, I dropped off.
I was getting stoned.
That's okay, mommy.
Mommy.
I know.
oh my good lord did you get that five dollars psyche i sent it to you
you did thank you so much i appreciate you you're welcome i appreciate you
here's the arthur song where did wane though wane left
and chase the drama the drama pays him rent one of the two cars rome sideways like a fart and share
wrestler shouting
What is that song is about?
It's basically it's basically about yeah, it's basically about like I'm uh, I was saying that you look hot no, oh
Yeah, well
You're seeing Arthur. He was the clown shoes. He's there's Arthur the clown. He's a midget sometimes
No, I have that. Oh, you know she reminds me of the girl for cloudy with a chance of meatballs
Oh
value of the chance of meatballs ever seen that show rain or I'm sorry
Sorry, Joel. No
That's a movie not a show
You look like that girl from there
Not no she likes it man, she's
Okay
I had a good haircut I should make
Oh, he's gonna leave. I had a
What happened to ghost? Um, goes probably fell asleep on the toilet mom. I usually does. Yeah, cause he just asked me where was I said I'm back on the panel. I dropped off. You know, you know, beat me with a stick or something. I mean, I mean, he's just saying.
Is that is that things to be sir something? No, he's talking about things that is you have his
Oh, oh, yeah, yeah, you almost sound like you have the thunder
He's a bald woman
Highlighted for a long time
Definitely not me. I don't have nothing like that
You're lucky that's um, no L's boyfriend. Yeah
I think I thought like I was like, oh look at my life
That was it. It's a two likes and I then I liked it. I was
It's been like an hour and a half
Okay, I look at the ghost's back.
Ghost.
Ghost, save the show.
Save the show.
Ghost, can you save my show? We need some ghost.
I'm going to do a ghost song again, but...
I'll put it in the middle.
Close wait, what's your what's your diagnosis?
Psyche I have to get going but I'll join you back pretty soon. All right, thanks. It's me on the show. Do you have fun?
I had fun with you guys. Yeah
No, I'll join because no, I was here
I'll be back
What's the train? Where's the train at?
Where you're at? Oh my god.
It goes to the train station.
I'll be back and like give me a jiffy, you know, like give me like five minutes, whatever.
Hey, that was that was Mason on the drums. That's Mason?
Um, yeah, that was that was the noise you just heard that was Mason.
It was you.
All right, I'll see you guys. Okay, I'll see you guys. I'll see you, psyche.
It was great talking to you. Yeah.
And I have it as a clip where like I think it was like, oh, it's like, you know, this is playing the drops by boy
Thanks
Someone was playing the drops. Oh here
Same as the composers. Oh my god, yes, we have some new corn dogs backstage
It's like it might all
This is not easy. They're like, oh my god. What do you do? You don't wait? You don't work. I mean, how much work this is
Hello
corn dogs
Hi, what's up? Who is this?
Look, it's me corn dogs. Okay. Why are you wearing a ski mask? I don't wanna see man
Oh, I can't really see you
Okay. Oh, okay. I think you're okay. I'll take my okay. Oh my god. Yeah damn, man
corn dogs
He's not salmon, I think it was corn dog, not salmon.
Yes, I know him.
I know him, yes, I do.
Oh my God, it's Bradley, right?
I love Bradley.
It's Bradley.
Yeah, well, what do you think?
No, no, thanks
I have a boyfriend
What's this girl's name I know her
I know I know you too. No, well, we've been friends for years. Yes. We've been friends for a long time. Yes, we have
Good, how are you the same you have the same hairstyle? You're the same like mustache. No, thanks. I'm sorry
I'm not your me or friends
That we're saying I'm not your type
We are friend you were purple and you're a am I
Your type to be your friend. Is that a wig friends? Yes
I would never want anything out. No, is this a wig?
Is that a wig?
Gallagher character
I
That's his hair
Why would psych make fun of my hair like no say Kenny G I think make fun of my hair, too
Thank you jerk to me. I thought you were gonna be cool psych that lady doesn't know you're good. Yeah, I'm just
It's like that lady that does those streams about you is so crazy.
Oh, I know.
You've seen that, yeah.
Dude, I've been watching them and she talks about, I'm like, that's my homie she's talking
about.
That's my homie psych.
That's my, that, this guy, Psych Noelle has taught me about Tarot and told me what the
real meaning of cars are and he's a good man and I know he's a good man.
Thank you, but I mean I say I would be surprised. It's like, you know, she she charms you with that like, you know
That's siren call. She'll go
And then it's I mean, I mean don't work on me psych. You're my homie
You know it's like Ursula. Yeah, you know
She turns into that to that woman Vanessa and then which means butterfly and she tries to get away from Ariel
So she's gonna marry to her and then it's like she almost like dies and stuff
Yeah, exactly great great analogies like yeah, I'm bringing great. I'm turning
No, I'm never gonna betray you
I mean, it's like everyone has betrayed me
It's like I'm gonna forgive them, but it's like I'm like, you see what you see how he treats me. No, well, yes
He makes fun of my hair and then he says I say I'm never gonna betray you and he says oh you already
That's good. That's a real picture. I'm wearing Jeffrey Dahmer glasses.
Mentor of the rocket.
I'm gonna put on my housekeeper's glasses.
Okay.
It looks okay. So that's just some re on a rocket. Okay. That's cool
Fuck this AI slop shit though. Yeah, it's not a slop. I don't like that. I can't do that
Do you want to subscribe to my channel?
You that's gross
Will you come on my stream that's your hair? Yeah, of course. Yeah
I'm karaoke corndog karaoke corndog
Like if I put my channel in the back you put your channel down you in
Please this is me and the private chance. I'll do it. I'll do it. No, well, you know, well, how's life?
Good. How was you? And you have a boy who's your boyfriend?
Sackie here's a big silver boy from right here. No, well
What do you want me to do? That's the goat. Oh my god. No, that's a great. That's a it's a ram
Right. Hey psyche. I put my channel in the back. Okay. Thanks. I will subscribe to it
So it's like psyche. I also want to say one more thing. What?
I went to that liquor store that that crazy lady said that
you did not
My friends like he's a good man
They said, you know what?
There's people trying to tell us that he's not but we know he's a good man
Well, I don't know like her told me that they like you and they actually want you there. Thank you. I'll see you
That is mine corn dog. I just I just write to you
Yeah, she's very welcome
I'm just taking some stuff off the back. Yeah. Oh my god. You're here. What's that email you put in the back?
You know, well, you're switching numbers with guests. That's my YouTube channel. Okay. I guess that's okay.
Stinky. The corn dog. Yes. Why's your name stinky? That kind of sounds gross. Yeah, exactly. That's what I was going to say.
Because, like, I put it that way. Is it because you smell bad? No, I don't.
Oh, yeah, so I want to see this good times clip and it's like a bite. I mean, I can believe it already. I can
I just want to say I got like a horrible response from the person that I was doing homage to I was just trying to say wow
You know, you know, she's like so entertaining and such a presence like she can be parody and stuff
And she said, she said I'm the scum of the earth for doing this.
And she said, she said that he's so dumb for falling for it.
And he looked like an idiot and stuff.
And that was, that was worth it all.
So this is all in good times.
Hold on.
I'm gonna find Shane.
Oh, okay, right.
And this is, I'll just play a little bit of it
because it's like, wait, he believed it for hours.
It was so funny.
And then she's like, well, nobody,
she's like, nobody's laughing at you.
There's all, or with you, there is laughing at you.
Yeah, that's that
Okay, so
He still has it up
No, who are you talking about?
This is on good time show and he blew it so I came up a sweepy and he believes I was sweepy the whole time
So here it is. Oh, yeah
He still does a show. Yeah
What's his channel called what these shadows you know, so yes, I know him or
We're on 14 after being up for 14 hours or start to feel tired ish
Here you go somebody's back
Sweet pea. All right, let's I know that guy
Glasses on so I can see
uh covered up to make sure I'm not porn bomb they do on their camera anyways let me move this
can you chop good times channel so i can yeah i'm done
porn dog did you uh add me hold on listen listen yeah i know i said it's hard to you already
listen i'm all right uh i feel good i saw you on betas what on betas
No, I wasn't I wasn't a beat us. I don't
Oh a month ago probably a month ago, I don't go around there anymore. How are you?
Oh, I'm good. I'm feeling good. I quit drinking.
Congratulations. Yeah, I know it's looking at your voice. It's like can you look good?
Do you look like an applicant alert and, um, great.
Yeah, but knew a lot of laundry and cleaning my house.
I was a sweet, pretty good-looking man. Thank you.
There's sounds like you though. He can tell I don't like being anymore. She's like kind of like
I was modded before and then you took it away
Yeah, she started talking nasty me after a while. What's up clumsy
I don't, I don't like the drama cast. I don't like to be part of drama.
Yes, you guys.
To me, it's not entertainment. People yelling at each other, arguing,
or just talking shit on other people. I don't care about it.
Yeah, I was taking a break from all the drama community, but I like your show.
That's because I try to keep it chill.
Yeah, I like your music when you play
It's like it's like the 70s and 60s. It's like brings me back to to my childhood. That's a mix of all different types of stuff
Yeah, I play a lot of 80 stuff
This is whatever sometimes. I'll take it something put it on sometimes. I'll play rap music, you know, just depends on what type of mood
I'm in
When I say rap music, I mean it from the 90s not anything there
Oh, you like like the like the old school shit old school well old school is old school 90s
To me, that's not old school
But like easy easy. Yes, my two favorites are Tupac and easy
I love Tupac. I love it. I love that Hey Mama song.
Yeah, I've heard that one.
You've heard that one? Okay.
Yeah.
You against the world? You against the world? Is that your favorite? What's your favorite Tupac?
Well, the only album I owned was Don't Kill My Love. Don't Kill My Love.
It's like Illuminati, but it's like Don Killu.
Oh, Killuminati?
Oh, I know the Killuminati, this last album, I think.
It was a double CD, because two CDs, because he had a deal with Shug Knight.
Shug Knight got him out of prison for like $3 million or $3.5 million,
and he had to sign with Death Grow for a three album deal.
A double CD, he was able to get out of his feel quicker.
Yeah.
He was going to go start his own record label.
I like his hologram.
I want to touch his hologram.
Have you seen his hologram-y stuff?
Yeah, I know the guy that invented it.
I want one for my house.
Well, I don't know him personally, but I know him.
He's like, you can be in the same room as me
and perform every day, and I can.
I can pleasure myself to a Zapatar.
Okay.
So what else is new?
Do you know this woman, Christine?
I hate this cunt.
I mean, this cunt.
This is not a drama channel, but-
Well, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Bob, you don't like her, okay.
She used to pop in here once in a while.
She did.
But like, not a join, but she type in my chat.
Your friends once, she started making fun of my voice.
I know it's your voice is a little raspy.
It's a little raspy.
I went to a concert.
Okay, what'd you go see? I'll see you if you can I saw it was a Fleetwood Mac cover band, okay?
Hey, I'm on the pencil girls that are not taking calls
Uh-huh psyche. Thank you. Did you fall asleep? I'm here. Oh, okay. She's talking to you. No, well
Um, who is that girl in your profile, okay, I'll see a picture
Who's that beta? Do you talk to uh, hi
She's what
I N I N X.
Yeah.
Can you text me?
Oh, okay, well, that right now,
I'm almost falling asleep right now.
I'm so wet.
So I'm about to crash.
Probably tomorrow.
Tomorrow, I got some things to do in the morning.
I'm sorry.
At what time?
I was boring, I'm sorry.
Probably about one o'clock.
Are you gonna text me at that time?
Yeah, central standard time.
Okay.
Yeah.
Who there's no one named the Shadyam riser. Can you follow a riser? Who's that?
He's a he's just a stalker
You want her to follow a stalker
Well, that's what I think about stalkers is they always will follow you. Yeah, that's true. I can tell yes
Yeah, I think they're from the loyalty
You'll text you after okay home from church tomorrow Noel
No, you had a church Joe anywhere. Why are you texting Noel from after? What do you have your switching numbers with Noel?
Yeah, you realize they know well. No, you're allowed to date regular men. No, I did you see the Mary Carrie stuff last night?
What Mary Carrie?
No, do you mind me a little bit of you?
But yeah
I never heard of that person
Anyway, I went on for another 20 minutes with good times
It'd be easy to notice that I wasn't like a woman and even like this even if he's like good times
She's like that wasn't me
Tell I mean I could tell
She said you made a fool out of yourself and then she said at IRL
Look, look, try to sue him with this information.
I mean, it's like so crazy.
Oh my God, I can't take it.
No, I can't believe with the whole time. He didn't catch it at all. Like he really thought we were women.
No, he told me to go into the chat. He's like, no, you can't, yeah, because he eventually got so nasty, like with the sexual comments.
He got frustrated, but yeah, and then he kicked me off when I started like, I don't want to be double penetrated by Bronzeberg and Sandman and stuff.
That was basically it. Okay, so
But it's this I guess this is reminds me of this reminds me of a you
You know, well
Mary carry a little bit here. I'll see
Look at this date. So it's cute. So her mom is she has a mom and a grandma that are like
Everybody enjoyed this right for each other
I thought you two would be good together.
No.
Listen to Mary cackling in the background.
Yeah, that's kind of a weird thing.
But why don't we...
But she's never going to give Gary...
Off, off.
I could see...
Yeah, that your grandma Lee they provide you with a great life
So do you think you took the life of porno because you didn't have the love of your father and perhaps there was too much pressure in your life
And I just like to be son of attention. I just like to always, you know
Be in front of people and you're certainly getting my attention now. Yes
I don't know if you're interested, but I understand that grandma and mom do an unbelievable version of Farah Jhaka
Well, maybe we'll end with that. Would you guys like to do Farah Jhaka sing on him?
But where right here in the microphone sing fair as a jaca fair as a jaca door may boo door may
boo summer and Latina summer and Latina dad dad don't dad dad don't yeah
You've got an interesting story, you've got an interesting life.
In fact, I might option it for the movie of the week, but Gary, good luck on your date
with Judy.
Let's find out what happens.
Keep us posting kids and Lee, nice to meet you.
How they got something to give you I leave I'm not your coffee cup, but it says Oregon on it
You got a coffee cup all right bring anything for Judy
Give the coffee cup to Judy
Well now you're making time
All right, give a coffee cup to Robin and one to Judy
All right, well there it is the true story of Mary Kerry her mom and grandma and Gary the retard and mommy will be a
Bada bing also. Oh, she will come tonight. I that's I was told that my mom's coming with me. Really? Yeah, maybe she'll come on stage
I don't know you don't get naked in front of people. Do you know would you like to?
No.
All right.
What do you mean, no?
Well, maybe.
Hey, you know what?
I like girls when they get naked on the webcam.
Yeah.
He's on the web all the time.
All right.
You know what?
In fact, if you've got a computer,
I've got a webcam at home right now.
All you have to do is click on my name,
and I can send it to you.
See me on the cam.
I can see you naked.
Well, you want to see him naked?
I'll tell you what, if I could go on a website and see Gary The Retard naked, I might go
on there.
Gary The Retard.
All right.
MaryCarry.com.
Thank you.
And GaryTheRetard.com, I guess it is, or whatever.
www.com.
All right.
And we'll be back.
What is it, Doug?
Do you want to show the mother her daughter dancing?
I don't think so. No, no, I don't think she actually grasps the whole concept.
Well, I don't know that I don't know that she needs to.
She's going to the bottom bang club tonight.
She'll see her doing that.
Were you totally new to the bottom bang?
No.
Entopolis?
Okay.
All right, we'll be back right after these words.
All right, I met Gary.
We're going to go out and have a date.
We have a lot in common and I'm really excited about it.
Very happy about it.
Bye.
Let's go.
Come on.
Yeah.
Oh, she's on my...
You know that's what I think.
We're gonna go sit at the park and talk.
Oh.
She don't like to walk across the light.
She says, don't walk.
Yeah, I don't like to.
Nope.
She says, don't walk.
Yeah, I don't like to.
Nope.
That's in New York, you got breakfast here, you're gonna go sit at the park and eat,
and get to know each other a little bit better, so, you know?
You said you got breakfast here, you hungry?
Yeah.
Definitely hungry, huh?
You hungry? I'm hungry too.
I've been here since 12 o'clock last night.
No breakfast menu at this time.
Yeah, Mary, here's your breakfast.
Thank you.
Touch mine.
Mine's right here.
Eat.
You like it?
I like it.
I do too.
I'm hungry.
Mmm.
Ew.
You just finished your breakfast.
Grossed out.
Jeez.
Come on.
Let's see if you want to go home.
What's the matter?
I don't like him.
You don't like him?
What happened?
Red quick?
You guys are getting along great.
You should send a nice breakfast.
Just grab my type.
But you can't be friends, can't you have a friendly date?
No, I don't get it.
I don't know what's going on.
I don't do friends.
Let her go play daughter.
Alright, this isn't going well then, huh?
No.
Gary, did you say something?
No, I didn't say nothing to it!
But you guys were getting along five minutes ago, weren't you?
No, we weren't.
So was it all an act on the show?
Yep.
You never liked him to begin with?
No, I just didn't ever lose feeling.
I felt like a stupid, you know,
blankety blank fool the whole time.
Gary, what's going on?
He likes my daughter more than me.
Let him go with my daughter.
That's what you heard the feeling?
Yeah, let him go with my daughter.
I'm not gonna put out a big goddamn lie anymore.
Yeah, do you want to apologize?
I'm sorry.
What's going on here?
This is terrible.
Here's your daughter. Here's Mary.
I'm not gonna live a lie. I'm not gonna do a god damn lie anymore.
I'm not gonna go with them.
If they, it's finished. It's finished.
You just had a nice breakfast, didn't you?
What's the breakfast?
What's going on? This is terrible.
Fuck it! I am done with this damn asshole!
It's it! It's it!
I feel what the fuck was going on.
That's why!
No date, no nothing, ha ha, I like the other girl better, ha ha, she's more kidder, more
better, yes.
There you go.
All right, just in case you need an update, earlier we had on Pornstar, Mary Carey, her
retarded mother and slow grandmother, Gary the retard hooked up and Doug Goodstein has
been on their date videotaping it for television purposes.
Doug, you say the date has come to an end?
Okay, hello. Yes. Yeah, things have gotten out of control very quickly here. What happened?
Apparently, Judy was upset the entire time that Gary was hitting on Mary.
Mary carried the porno stars mother Judy was upset. Yeah. Yeah, so, you know, they left the studio
They were walking on and on down the street. They were getting on great
We took him to the park
They had a nice breakfast and then Judy sort of snapped and she she said
I've had enough only keep talking about with my daughter and she's very very very fired up
She's stormed away. We had to pull her back and I think that they pretty much over
And Gary's sitting here, he looks a little dumbfounded.
Well, it's not a great strategy to get a woman by hitting on her daughter.
I mean, but isn't it like true that all guys, even if you're retarded, instead of going for
the sure thing, he goes for the younger daughter.
I've done it a million times.
Gary's a smart guy.
Do you want to talk to anyone?
I do. I want to first speak to Gary.
But he's a classic case of going on.
I think you have two lines up, so you can pot up the second one.
I have two of you over here.
All right.
Is the second one up? Is it working?
No, it's not.
Bye. Stand by.
Let me just talk to Gary.
Gary.
Gary, I heard the date came to an end.
You can't hit on the daughter in front of the mother.
I know.
I know that.
Why did you insult her like that?
I don't understand. I know. I just had never seen her.
Never seen her. We're okay.
Well, I tried to hook you up
A woman
Attractive you're always talking about how you want a girlfriend, right and what you did was you hit on her daughter the entire time
Damn, no, I can't help you if you're gonna do that. I know I know that were you not attracted to the mother
Do you want to go apologize to her?
All right, let me speak to Judy
Okay
Never been so humiliated in my life Judy. I've never been so humiliated in my life
That scary was coming out to my daughter the whole time in the studio
D start handicapped man. They always want to get off their league
I'm not retarded, I'm not, but I'm not low.
Just have, have some other people that know me.
I've never been so humiliated in my life.
No, I don't like the date.
No, no, I don't like it.
It wasn't a good day.
Hey, Judy, it was not a good day.
No.
Well, Judy, by the way, I don't think you're retarded.
Your daughter told us that you were retarded.
Well, I don't know if that's not true.
All right.
But she's absolutely right.
These handicapped men are trying to go out of their league.
That really gets me.
Well, Judy, let me tell you something.
I figured Gary was very lonely.
Your daughter told me about you.
I said, what the heck?
Let's fix these two guys up, see if it works out.
I think you're very pretty.
I think you're a nice woman.
And the fact that Gary acted inappropriately is wrong.
I don't care if I ever did again in my whole life if I looked at the 110 I will never get a guy like Gary never
Well, I think Gary owes you an apology doesn't he?
I don't have to would you like that would you I would like Gary to apologize to you
Would you allow him to do that? Yes, and then I never want to see him again. Oh, so you wouldn't be a nice guy mommy
He's nice
People are nice doesn't mean they're right for each other. I thought you two would be good together
No, listen to Mary cackling in the background. Yeah, that's kind of a weird thing
But why don't we she's never gonna give Gary another chance, huh? Yeah
I don't I know I don't think that's gonna happen Gary. Are you there as well Gary? I
Want to hear his apology
He did something wrong
They're like my daughter, but that's not his fault.
I just don't like these handicapped men
trying to get out of their league all the time.
They act like they're done gifts to women.
Well, it's true. I mean who Gary the retard who hasn't had a date and ages all of a sudden is acting like Don Juan
I agree with you
Yeah, we're just watching a little bit of like an old Howard Stern clip with like, you know
It's like Mary Cary porn stars to just 21 years old at the time
I joined psyche just so I could talk to you
So you have a thing for are you like are you mentally?
I have a little crush on psyche is that's all right
Okay, well, how old are you, you're 21 years old, are you trying to go for the legal system or something?
No, I just don't, I mean, I'm being accused of all kinds of things, you know?
You're aware, you're what, you're 21?
So you're two years old?
No, no, no.
If I'm if I'm freaking you out and you're gonna get freaked out about them like yes
No, no, no, I mean, I say no, I mean it's like it's fine because you know what it's like
I'm actually like I think people are just like overblowing like right little thing. So you're scared
Has no power because they say it to literally everybody but it's like just annoying. No, why why why do you find it offensive?
Because I do.
But worse crime to the worst, like, doing the worst crime.
No, why do you find it offensive?
I don't have a criminal record.
Is it because I don't make music?
No.
Because I have a boyfriend.
Oh damn it. Isn't it the fucking damn scientists that fucking creates all that fucking?
No.
Does anyone want to date Noel? But I think only Mason is allowed to date me.
No, thank you.
Is it the damn scientist that makes all of the food fall from the sky? Is that your boyfriend?
Yeah, that was the other one.
I'm off-limit.
I'm the mayor. I'm the mayor.
I'm the mayor.
I'm off-limit.
Okay, you like you've been accused of liking cheese. I mean
Okay, you're out you're off limits for the show bye, okay
Well the date is over
You are someone's got to slap Mary
Mary just laughs the entire time at her mother.
Terrible.
What?
Doug?
That's still here.
Oh, Gary, are you going to apologize or not?
Yeah, for this guy.
I apologize to her, but she wasn't sick.
Go ahead and do it again.
I did, I did, but she wanted to stuff you out.
Thank you. What the hell are you watching, bro?
I just wanted to join you, but George, other kids, too.
That's Mary, Mary, they feel she were James.
He likes Mary, Carrie. Absolutely.
Thank you. What the fuck are we watching, bro?
You shut up between them. That's who we really wanted.
No, well, they didn't spell her name right.
I always want to get out of goddamn league.
Oh, no.
Well, you know, Gary, Judy makes a good point.
Hey, Judy, why is your daughter always laughing?
She really bugs me too. I've never been so humiliated with my life.
Ask her why she's always laughing.
I guess it's better than crying.
Oh my goodness. I feel you.
What a family. The daughter's the porn star she laughs.
She laughs at the mother and the grandmother. No respect.
Well, Judy, uh, I'm, I'm waiting to hear God's apology.
Yeah, I would like to hear it again.
Gary, sweet talker a little, Gary, don't listen.
Just keep talking.
Just tell her you're sorry, please.
She's right. Why are you laughing at her every minute?
All right, listen, this date has gone.
Gary, were you enjoying the date?
Mary, why did you go on the date?
Yeah, Mary.
First number one, let me tell you.
I thought we were going to a nice restaurant.
I thought the whole crew was just going to a nice restaurant.
I didn't know a whole stupid crew was going to follow us around
with cameras in the park.
I feel like a complete, complete fool.
I got to tell you.
I I thought it was gonna go. I you know, I didn't know what to think Judy
I just thought that Gary was lonely. You were lonely and I thought maybe it'd be a good
Right well you were very gracious you said you liked Gary you thought that maybe there could be a love connection
But obviously it didn't work out
from the beginning, right? You didn't like him from the beginning?
I just didn't want to hurt his feelings. Give me credit.
Well, Gary, you've struck out again. You lost the daughter, you lost the grandmother, and you
lost the mother. You lost three women today. You struck out on three bases. You played it all wrong.
You're out. You played it all wrong. Come on. You're definitely no ladies man, Gary.
But you know, you know, it's been so long since I've been with the women, you know.
I know.
Nice.
All right.
Okay.
Judy, nice meeting you.
I'm sorry it didn't work out.
All right.
And Gary, I think you blew it.
I think Judy would have been a good love match for you.
But what can I say?
You're going home to Oregon alone again.
The heart wants with the heart wants.
So, what happened?
You said it well.
You ever hit that with Mason?
Because last time I said that, you started repeating, um, no, I'm protected.
I mean, would you start saying over and over again?
I didn't know you were like, I'm off limits.
I'm off limits.
Why'd you start reacting like that?
Because I am.
Yeah.
But that's Mason.
I mean, it's like, he has a woman almost in his whole life.
I do not care.
Okay.
That's him, not me.
Okay, I thought you are like her for the make-a-wish foundation. No. No
You just made nightmares come true not wishes. Oh, can you hear me? Hello, it's Sweepie. It's your friend Sweepie. Okay. Well, she's not gonna laugh
I don't know. It's not like she's getting a bad night. She's really bumming me out. Is that Mace in the drummer boy? Yeah
And you can listen to the music from backstage
he's behind the drums keeping perfect time then starts another pointless argument online
technically actually historically speaking brother nobody else is another debate he's
Huh, you kicked her off forcing to who to you or that guy was not annoying
She's just saying they didn't like and then it's just bothered me to the point where I was just like, okay
And she had a big she had a big frown on her face and she was in turning upside down. Oh
Okay, yeah, but oh
Do you want to ask her about the branding? I think Brandon, he was was east talking her or
something. I don't know if we're looking for that again. He's talking her right now? Well, he
wouldn't she say she says she say he like he um he's he wanted to show her his penis.
Now I don't remember what she said but she was laughing about it so we can really believe it.
What's that? Sometimes laughter is a response to trauma. Well, no, I'll come back here. You can explain
Yeah, but she said that she met him, you know, or whatever and you know, it didn't make sense
I think she traveled to New Mexico
I don't know. Oh, yeah, who knows? He acted like he didn't know who she was
But yeah, who knows because that guy's a weirdo. I mean
We'll never really, she is a mystery, you know, I met her at like a science and like, you know
And now she's like, you know, basically, she's just a little bit smarter than Vita at this point.
Yeah, man. Yeah, it's so, it's so good, but yeah.
Sorry, someone says you're going after Crystal, still someone says you please.
No, I'm not going to. No, I talked to her a couple days ago. She even asked me to call her.
So she's pretty mad about Jamie, but she keeps flip-flopping all the time. She doesn't know who it is
She's after because she was talking about Jamie and Nancy allotted
Somebody showed Nancy's true colors. Everything Barb said about Nancy was true
I think what they do is they put out some horrible clip that gets me or you or somebody else upset
because it's like so incendiary and terrible that she deletes it real quick and then it's just our
reaction is out there and then she does some innocent thing. Who are you talking about? Who?
I'm just saying that's a tactic of the media and you know we only have a few media.
Yeah, yeah, just don't keep reacting though. You know like I know but I'm a reaction channel
So it's kind of like I know but she hadn't been on live for two days
So and you keep still reacting just just I know because every day she puts that under a new clip or with new information
That I need to react to she's I guess
And she said I was a pedophile because I shared follow that bird
Yeah, but before that but she hadn't been around at all yesterday or today
And you're still reacting to always around. I have caught her stalking and inside my chat hiding so many times
Videos on you just you know, don't keep making more videos. It's just too much because I'm
Me I'm responding to those but she didn't make any yesterday. She hadn't been live
But I didn't make one yesterday either
But I know but you're still got videos and then you're live earlier today. You mentioned her
You tell me you tell me to keep good receipts and stuff, right?
Yeah receipts, but she's hasn't been on yesterday at all and you're still making more videos and mentioned
Yeah, that's what i'm saying. I thought you left it alone after you went on on uh,
Yeah, so I just believe it because other people just want to keep that on they wanted to keep it up
Okay, so yeah next never mind the wish beware of the cat
Yeah, exactly good thing
So and then there's other instigators that are shady as hell and they're the ones who wants out for like crystal
You know, she's really pretty she's been talking to everybody
The name of like a drug, you know, yeah, and so it is interesting
Yeah
You know that we've crystals to and so yeah
you ever noticed like drugs are kind of like candy like you know like people like you know
candy is kind of like training almost like like for drugs because it's like
it's so sweet and like sugary and it's all bad for you and it's like you know and all this weird
Like fun like little things ways to like eat it and stuff. I don't know. Yeah
There might you have drugs kids candy like drugs
Yeah, but there's some very toxic people like the crystal look at all the wars that she starts and turns on everybody and then
I'm saying
Poisoning from all those rubber babies you pushed out of yourself, you know, yeah
Yeah, I don't know I just said though, but if she hasn't changed at all, she doesn't do real life and she just
It's just it's the same bullshit.
I mean, I'm just real life is
difficult. I mean, I'm ready.
I'm ready for a fake life. I
mean, you know, you know, just
try not to react and just do
you know, because I've been
there, you know, I know how it
is and you just get so mad. You
gotta show more. I was going to
put through one of the and then
one of but one of Christine
Yeah, yeah, I don't know. I wouldn't even trust me. It's a good troublemaker
Yeah
Yes, you're nice new litter box for my cat. Oh you did you got a new one? Yeah, it's really nice. Yeah
Good. It's like a whole system
I still have to, I'm still moving stuff around.
Oh, yeah, but no, I want to show,
but yeah, it managed to be, it's weird as well.
Yeah, like the baby, you know, she's still a young baby,
though, so I was giving her regular cat food,
but I ordered her some kitten food,
because you know, she's gonna have kitten food
for at least a year, though,
and so she's around four months old, you know,
she's got a few months to go.
Inax, what did the cat say when it thought somebody was joking with her?
What? What do you mean?
Like what did the cat say? Is it just a joke?
You say what? What did they say?
They said, are you kidding me?
Oh, kidding cat.
Are you kidding me?
You're seeing this picture, I think they found this picture of a salmon and elbow.
Did you see that one?
Oh, that's supposed to be both of them.
Eldo and Salmon.
Yeah, I saw the picture of Eldo.
Yeah, that they put up there.
I don't know why.
It's kind of like kind of sexy, though.
I don't know.
Oh, really?
You have this picture?
I had them, and now I'm just going to get turned on when
I look at it.
Well, what does this picture look like?
I want to see.
I know it was on the live the other day, and I recorded it,
but I haven't looked at it yet.
The original is that they're Siamese twins.
I think they have the original picture of them.
No, I think you you were showing a picture of him that you were playing a clip and and it was
And he was mad because somebody was using his picture and I didn't realize that was his picture
Yeah
Okay
Hi, I'm Sweet Pea. How nice to meet you.
You know, my time is believed that I was a woman for over an hour yesterday.
You know that? And he almost said I can move in, but he said no.
And I'm, because I'm banter on it normally, but he let me out.
I was like, I'll tell him that.
And I think he'll pull him again in the future because, I mean, it's like that all was like...
ridiculous
He said I was backstage like jerking off on his I would not never do that
Yeah, I
Mean not for him
Yeah
Damn
Oh, have you heard of Kentucky's?
There you heard of conduct home Kentucky. Let me see. Oh my god. What is this?
What is what is it?
Oh my gosh, I think I have to do a PSA there's another thing I have to do a PSA
Oh, I thought you were going to show the picture the picture you were going to show
Yeah, this is a young Crystal Anne
And I want to show this video. They said I just have to do a PSA for
This organization in just a second. I said the word I wasn't supposed to say so certain word, you know, I mean
So who sent the cement to crystal? They said they sent it to her twice really retarded
Will you believe me? Will you turn away?
They are six million rental retarded Americans who need to be helped who can't be helped
Who's helping the art the association for retarded citizens?
They helped me
Yes, I am mentally retarded
Bill the art when you give help you give hope that her grifting in a commercial pretending
There's so many balsam products
But vanilla balsam
Yeah, who do you think sent the cement she said that they sent the cement to her twice
Yeah, I have I have the I have the video where she says you want to hear where she gets the cement sent to her
Yeah, we're here and I didn't know about that. She told me
Yeah, I have it. Yeah, I want to know I didn't I didn't know about that like it's called it. It's so funny
Didn't they do that to beat a year ago? I think
Yeah, and they have it and it's all documented where she refers she had a pizza delivery
You would think that she had well then she can build do something about it. That's still harassment. They paid for it
So I mean
Track them down, but yeah, I mean it's like after the class at class action. It's so this is called be this night of horse
Okay, so it's gonna still tie you to that count. It's a bank account still so yeah, even cash up. They'll still
Yeah, they should
Well, here's you're not drinking coffee in the morning. I guess they're just afraid to do a police report or do something about it
He's only like too much usually
Yeah, some people are really too scared to do anything about it. So there you sit there and let it happen
You're telling me that I'm laughing at you and all this shit. This is bullshit
Totally making shit up. This is fucking retarded because you're going at everybody with nonsense absolute bullshit
You don't say that I'm a stormy avalanche
Ali keep on bombin'
Say that I'm a stormy avalanche
Thank you.
Can you shut the fuck up and not make fun of people ever?
They're doing your fucking job.
Just shut the fuck up, you fucking bitch-ass fucker.
Listen, can you report that?
I didn't order pizza.
And I, I'm sorry.
I know it's not much, but please, I'm sorry.
Okay?
Good night.
The fucking jokes, this motherfucking thing that is.
I got fucking my alcohol and at the same time,
I'm trying to conclude, I didn't order pizza
when I get a pizza delivery.
And he wants to talk to the chat
about what he fucking thinks he should talk about.
Like, are you fucking dumb as fuck?
Let me fucking like actually not for us and bother people I
Ordered a white cloth. I received that the dude asked me for an ID. I said, I'm sorry
I smell like onions because I was cooking something and then I got this I like I got it. Look
I got it, but I didn't order pizza. Okay
I didn't so do not just keep yapping when I'm fucking trying to tell you or just like just go with the content
Like what the fuck is going on here? And he's like just going on like going on thing that is
Like do you understand like there's a possibility that I'm getting a harass and I was I'm getting pizza in my house
And you're just joking around with that
Like what the fuck is wrong with you? I don't get it. I really don't get it
Are you okay? Are you okay in truck?
Why are you laughing?
The door dash is on my door
Can I speak now he knows I did it I'm saying is it okay for you when I'm trying to talk to actually
Door dashes on my door like that one of them that I ordered and the other one
That's a fucking asshole. You're just gonna make fun of it. Is that what you're gonna do like what the fuck is wrong with you?
the fuck
Like way to protect me or care about my fucking safety way to fucking chair
Like the fuck are you done? Are you okay? No, it's time for you to go and smoke your cigarette
And I don't know do what you need to do. You don't give a fuck about my fucking life
The fuck are you okay? Are you okay thing that is?
Is it okay for you to fucking like argue with like people that are at my door?
I'm already having confusions
Do you see what just happened to me?
Yeah, I was here for it. I have two people my fucking
Ordered delivery and I had a somebody older pizza and you're yelling background
Like I'm trying to resolve shit, and you're just fucking talking
I don't know to the tab or me or the delivery, but you understand what's going on
Yeah
I get it if you live at my house and we look together and you're my husband and you come out of the bedroom
And you're upset, but you're in the fucking panel. You understand that I'm trying to deal with shit already
You understand that?
You're insane. Like you're absolutely insane. I'm insane or are you fucking like absolutely fucking intrusive?
Are you fucking not? Do you see I'm insane or is like what just happened to me insane?
Like
You know what you cried about me about some fucking something that never even was that important like funky
Being upset at you. I have a fucking legit fucking people sending pizza to my house and you don't think I should be upset
Go fuck yourself, you piece of shit.
What a fucking idiot.
I never said that.
So you're just making shit up now.
You're just making shit up now.
This is what you do.
You make shit up.
I make up fucking accents and names.
I make up names and accents.
I'm telling you, there's people at my fucking house.
Everybody sees it.
Get the fuck out of here.
The fuck?
I wore your fucking white cloth and here comes like fucking pizza and he's saying I'm insane.
Have a little bit of fucking compassion. Fuck you piece of fucking shit. If it happened to you
you would have a little bit more compassion wouldn't you? No you wouldn't.
You don't care although I attract like the worst fucking like friends ever
The words and especially when it comes to fucking man
I'm telling you like this is the last like minute. You should be even fucking like talking right now
I'm trying to fucking handle a motherfucker
Like like like all these fucking orders are being sent to my house and I only ordered one and I'm insane
I'm insane
I'm in fucking saying
Fuck you at the end of the day. I'm not as insane as people like fucking psyche that you joined your fucking panel
You know what? I'm not gonna fucking suck dick or a piece of pizza
I want to make my own fucking food. That's all I was doing. I'm insane
Fuck you and your fucking insanity
Fuck you and fuck what you stand for a piece of shit. The fuck I'm insane
You guys I swear to God. This is why I
Miss and I cannot ever ever like replace because I replace it with the fucking internet
somebody like my
Treatment man, I mean
What the fuck are you guys doing?
Don't do that, don't.
Don't.
I know this fucking Asian fucking girl with the Mexican guy all twisted together
Like I'm trying to work it out and I have somebody like fucking this fucker over there like yelling and screaming bad
fucking, I'm just saying, hold on, let me deal with this.
I was supposed to like, actually be there and tell you guys what
the reality of my life, when I get fucking constant shit sent
to my house, I'll call it like I paid for it. But nobody is
good as an alcohol to my house. They always send food and all
this shit whether it's paid for it or not. And then I have a
Telling me I'm fucking insane.
I got another goon as mad like Samma who fucking thinks I'm crazy and they use my fucking name.
Leave me the fuck alone. All you motherfuckers don't know could be here.
I can live on my own.
And then I like to get this motherfucker telling me I'm insane.
Go sit in your Canadian little cave.
Go
You would never know
How insane shit fucking gets if you were me you already been in a fucking
Cuckoo ranch. You don't know. I'm not insane. I'm fucking strong. I
Know I learned the fucking hard way, but hello
I get people chances and you calling me fucking insane for fucking like telling you to shut the fuck up
I don't know what's going on over here. Get the fuck out of here. Get out of here
Get out of here
In your mouth before bed to rebuild damaged teeth from the inside out and shock your dentist
Did you know there is a natural way to?
Don't want that fucking sit there and like condone this shit and think it's fucking funny go fuck yourself
Go fuck yourself
Go fuck yourself, like I got two people at my door at the same fucking time
And I got a fucking hyena over there joking in the chat. I'm like, yeah, I don't know
I think it's hilarious. No concern about my fucking safety. How I fucking feel at that moment
It's ridiculous. I'm live, I'm not fucking live.
When I'm live, it's even worse. I get it worse even when I'm live.
When I'm live, I get it worse. Be a fucking man.
Oh, he's crying man
Fucking pieces of shit you don't want to come across somebody like my fucking axe
He would fucking destroy every single one of you you guys are pieces of shit
trolling playing around on the internet
joking around because you have no guts no balls none of us none of us none of us hold on we got
another one hold on actually stop crying real quick hi i didn't order anything can i take a picture
Can you um
Filming this I stream and third person three people tonight I came to my house. I know that's my address
Like I didn't order anything
Okay, sorry, thank you. Sorry, I didn't order anything from Patrick
Jesus fucking cry
Keep doing it
I'll document it. I'll document it. Oh, sorry guys. I got another one. This one was from Peshko. I didn't look in the bag. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
All doctor meant to beat up the black earthy. What's your fucking ass? You're not gonna tell me what to do on a panel
Okay, scams. I'm on. It's you're definitely not gonna control me and use my fucking name
Very hurry hurry. What's up?
An old video, right? Do you think I'm going? Oh
Okay
I already fucking told you what you did was cowardly
and every single mother fucker one of you
and say, oh, I like this person
and I like what they stand for
and you just like giggling and you're over there.
Bitch, don't come to me crying
about spunky or anybody else.
Don't.
When I needed you and like you were supposed
to fucking get it and I had two people on my fucking door.
Yeah, what?
I said a police a pizza guy showed up at the same time. How coincidental I kind of knew you that you were being trolled beta
What the fuck?
Holy shit
You're making shit up. You're telling me that I'm laughing at you and all this shit. This is bullshit
Totally making shit up
Know you've been drinking and I know you get emotional a lot shit
But this is fucking retarded because you're going at everybody with nonsense absolute bullshit
Put the bottle down be done fuck sakes
That's what you got to say for yourself, right after all the shit you've said about everybody
You're just gonna hide. Hey, that's the way to do it, right?
Put them backstage say fucking bullshit about them and then hide when they fucking confront you about it
I just like hanging out with her and she goes fucking nuts like this
And we've all kind of gotten to know you know that okay, you know when she's drinking she gets a little wild and we all kind of like just kind of
You know hang back whatever, but then she keeps fucking poking and poking with nonsense
people
People lose patience beta
Be the number white fucks. Thanks
I'm going to go ahead and crash some of it so yeah good so okay all right you
have a good night all right bye bye we care about our creative partners we
uh it's always it's always fun to have a next people on the show like me i'm
sweepy i would be on other channels too okay um so
I mean, I'm sure like nobody wants to hear anymore of this, but it's just so important to get this message out.
Imagine logging into a live stream and hearing a peer accused of stalking, smoking meth,
and actively plotting physical harm against an unborn child.
The host even invokes the term feticide to describe the alleged threat.
This is the reality of a specific broadcast from the in real life, or IRL, streaming community.
The host, Alexander Mayers, directed these heavy allegations at a fellow creator known
online as Psyche.
On one side ones have to weigh of legal charges like stalking and fetal homicide.
On the other side sits the actual evidence provided during the broadcast,
a few tiny chat bubbles and scattered video clip URLs that fail to move the needle.
This footage serves as an active case study in digital defamation,
where the narrative of a violent crime is constructed out of fragments of digital noise.
Understanding these mechanisms is the only way for a viewer to recognize how a creator can systematically dismantle a peer's reputation
by weaponizing the collective paranoia of their audience.
The host's strategy relies on a foundation of perceived vulnerability.
Throughout the broadcast, she uses her identity and her hope for a future pregnancy as a rhetorical shield,
framing any potential conflict as an attack on an unborn child.
By invoking the gravity of this federal law, the host escalates a standard internet feud into a life-or-death scenario,
regardless of whether a pregnancy has actually occurred.
This sets a psychological trap for the viewers.
Any attempt to question the host's narrative or ask for proof of her claims automatically casts the skeptic as an accomplice to potential harm.
Weaponizing vulnerability in this way effectively silences dissent.
The accuser gains immunity from standard criticism.
while the target is left unable to provide a defense
without appearing to minimize the safety of a mother and child.
A shift in language marks the next phase of the campaign.
The host avoids the target's name entirely, instead referring to Psyche repeatedly and
obsessively as Karen Lyon's responsibility.
Refusing to use a person's name is a deliberate choice to strip them of their humanity.
In this narrative, the target is no longer an individual, but a burden that someone else
is failing to manage.
This network diagram illustrates how the attack is redirected.
and routes attacks into a peripheral node, a third-party caretaker named Karen Lyons.
By inciting real-world harassment against a caretaker,
the smear campaign attempts to sever the target support system.
This isolation is a critical goal, leaving the target without the resources needed
to withstand a sustained public attack.
This proxy harassment bypasses digital boundaries,
The pressure on these third parties is designed to force the primary target to choose between
their own defense and the safety of their friends or family. The effectiveness of the smear depends
on the deliberate miscontextualization of the evidence. When we examine the footage presented
as proof of violence, we find only a clip of Psyche offering a pathetic self-deprecating apology to
The second piece of evidence is a clip of him alone in an empty room,
performing a bizarre comedy bit about transitioning and changing his name to Alexandra Bates.
This high-angle view of International Drive in Orlando shows a bustling tourist hub.
The host claims that the associates of the streamer stalked her right here with firearms in their backpacks,
a narrative that stands in sharp contrast to the awkward, isolated performance shown in the video evidence.
She reframes this cringe-worthy behavior, a creator making jokes to a silent tat room, as a criminal threat.
A sad comedy bit becomes a literal plot involving identity theft and physical harm.
When awkward social interactions are reframed as imminent criminal threats,
the broadcast moves beyond self-expression.
It crosses the legal threshold and enters the realm of actionable defamation.
Slander in the digital age is not confined to a chat room.
These tactics have immediate, tangible consequences for the people involved.
This aerial view shows Redondo Beach, California.
The host explicitly stated her intent to escalate this manufactured conflict to local detectives,
attempting to pull municipal law enforcement into a live stream dispute.
This escalation wastes actual public resources.
Beyond that, it threatens the target's livelihood and personal freedom based on nothing more than out-of-context video clips and unsubstantiated claims.
This places the burden of discernment on the audience.
In an internet ecosystem where outrage algorithms reward victimhood narratives,
viewers must look past the emotional delivery to see the facts.
Character assassination is executed in broad daylight
by creators who weaponize the language of victimhood
to dismantle a peer's life before a live audience.
Recognizing the playbook is the first step towards stopping the smear.
Okay, everybody, Apollo is here.
From Mount Olympa to the YouTube Scree
Here comes Apollo, land pristine
Spartan heart, helmet shining, confidence bright
Ask him who won, he's always right
I'm the season coming and rolls his eyes, Christine says
Here come another ten replies, he lifts his shield
and strikes a pose, I brought the
Heaves with twelve new Spartan friends
Toe the two tight beard looking clean
Dancing like the fiercest warrior ever seen
The DJ shouts, this one's for Greece
Apollo drops his shield and releases the beast
One heroic spin, two drinks in the air
Zeus yell down the-
He's some house-
brings receipts. Christine brings facts. Apollo brings a 40-minute counterattack. Commons keep
scrolling. Keyboards glow. Nobody remembers how the arguments started, though. But when
trouble-
Joe Shipley Joe Shipley came rolling with a Gemini grand one twin cause trouble the other joined in a ginger hair
Joker with a wild point of view by carry your spirit just seeing what was true
I had this armpits raised up to the sky. He won't like a trophy never telling this why
Funny as hell with a master troll degree. Nobody worked the chat room quite like Joe Shipley. Oh, Marilyn
Down by the river where the cool is blow Kim was his best friend
Loyal and true, a real one beside him and whatever he do
It rave him running underneath the tall trees Joe laughed like thunder on a Chesapeake Breeze
Gemini, heart living wild
That was Marilyn joe ship. He looked at state park in the old river shore where the water kept calling them back for more
Raven was his dog his shadow one pride always chasing sticks by the riverside when the sun went down and the drinks came around
Silly drunk Joe was the king of the town. He tell one joke. They forget we're related and laugh so hard and nothing that is
Oh face turn red. Oh
Down by the river where the cool winds blow
Kim was his best friend, loyal and true
A real one beside him and whatever he do
With a raven running underneath the tall trees
Yo laugh like thunder on a Chesapeake Breeze
Gemini heart living wild and
That was Maryland show ship. He controlled the whole room with a wink and a line that swear wasn't me
I was fishing the whole time Kim knew the truth, but we'll laugh anyway while Raven chase shadows at the end of the day
He never let a label tell him who we should be by Curious Joe follow curiosity a little bit
With a devilish part living this truth down in Maryland State Park. Oh, Maryland Joe let the river roll on
Carry every joke from the dust to the don't
Raise one for Raven and one for Kim
The loyal best friend who stood beside him
For the ginger germinine with the mischievous smile
Who made every gathering worth staying a while
Wild warm hearted and proudly carefree
Here's to Maryland, Joe Shepley
Where the river runs silver, underneath the old trees
You can still hear the laughter of Joe Shepley
Then rolls in like a fever dream
Eric Abadou had Elvis Green
Dr. Paporeca prescribes the vibe
Bill Gates, Wallach, Easter Bunny, and Ice
Poor boy swagger, Santa laugh
Tire rolling circus on a bubble bath path
Showed his butt once, world stood still
Chat lost, it's mine, algorithm 3
Of this mad land
Trust him with the chat no fear no fuss when trolls appear he turns them to dust skinny like a wire strong like myth
I put the cosmic twins supermodel live stream sanity if madness is art then he's the verse
And here it is the greatest advance in television since color television itself
See all color shows in living color
Once you've adjusted fine tuning
So there we see that it means that you can subdue a people
You can control a people by secret influence that goes on to say under charm to subdue by secret power, especially by that which pleases and delights the mind.
So under charm there it says power to subdue opposition and gain the affections.
How the Wicked Witch was having difficulties of doing her opponent, and finally she said,
I know what I should do, but take this crystal ball.
She spreads her hands across the crystal ball, and she creates a lovely puppy field.
So beautiful.
Dorothy, a lion, a scarecrow, going across this lovely puppy field all to one.
Is it possible that I, that's not just story, is it possible that the crystal ball sits
in the living room of every hole practically, and that it comes from a place called Hollywood?
In today's video, I would like to discuss Hollywood and its cold, satanic, illuminati,
and witchcraft roots.
Let's begin by understanding where the name Hollywood even came from.
The mainstream sources tell us the name Hollywood Land was coined by H. Whitley, who is also
known as the father of Hollywood Land in the 1800s.
It was not until 1902 when filmmakers started moving to Hollywood Land to see the harsh
and strict rules imposed by Thomas Edison's Emotion Picture Patents Company in New Jersey
And it wasn't even until 1923 when finally filmmakers themselves dropped the last four letters of Hollywood land and began calling it simply Hollywood.
So in essence, Hollywood was actually coined by the filmmakers themselves.
And I'm knowing that we can actually presume that Hollywood was a very sinister movie.
And in fact, the cold symbology behind Hollywood's name has a very interesting and different explanation.
The Druids were tree worshippers, and the Holly tree was their most sacred symbol because it was sacred to their mother, Holly or Hell, which is their Norse goddess of the underworld.
So we have holly or holly wood.
We also have held wood, the place of magic.
It is also very important to note that magic wands were always made out of the wood of a holly tree.
It's literally made out of holly wood.
Hollywood is a true critic establishment, guys, and metaphorically, these wands are used to make
movies like Magic. With a wave of a wand and a spell, Hollywood actually produces these magical
movies that become so famous throughout the whole world.
I mean, even think of a Mickey the magician waving his wand and passing spells on children
all throughout the world.
This Hollywood industry is literally a bunch of occultists, Satanists, and dark magicians
and sorcerers.
So, let's dive into a few of the symbols surrounding Hollywood and their hate.
And the first thing I really want to mention is one of the most recognizable symbols of
Hollywood and of all the elite around the world, and that is the red carpet.
We often see all of these world leaders and celebrities walking upon a red carpet.
And this is an old symbol dating back through the concocted story of Zara and Perez of the
time of the Druids.
The red carpet is a motif representing the royal blood path, or blood line, coming down
from the past and running the future.
This actually represents the 13 Illuminati bloodlines that we've all heard of.
They have been rulers of the world for ages and eons.
The 13 bloodlines date all the way back to all of these world leaders,
from British and French kings to Egyptian pharaohs.
They are basically all royalty and all the current leaders of the world are all to a point related.
There are four prestigious awards that an artist
or actor can win.
In an order from least important to most important,
there are the Golden Globes for recognition in TV and film,
for Rammys for music and musical achievements,
Rammys for television shows, and of course the Oscars,
which are the most glamorous awards
and are for the biggest movies of the year.
So let's cut to the chase and talk about some symbology between the two of the highest awards
Someone can actually obtain in Hollywood
So the second most important are the National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences
Which are also known as the Emmys and if you pay very close attention to the abbreviation of the National Academy
If TV, arts, and sciences, you get the word not toss, which is actually Satan backwards.
My brothers and sisters, this is not a sheer coincidence. I believe when a celebrity has
achieved this award, it is because their show is obviously, and of course, very popular throughout
We have heard many greats admit that they feel a spirit come over them when they are acting or singing.
And these celebrities say they feel as though their bodies have been taken over.
Guys, the bigger the demon that takes over, the more popular their show becomes.
There is strong evidence that when an actor gets an achievement this big and notoriety of that status,
it is because they have acted out a specific ritual, perhaps successfully pushed the anti-price
agenda throughout the media and onto the people, which in fact is of course helping Satan to cause
chaos and destruction onto this world. Whether the celebrities know what they're doing or not
is a different topic of all in itself, but I strongly believe that most or under some type of
whether MK Ultra, some demonic influence or even both. So let's take a look at the picture of
this Emmy Award Golden Trophy. Here we can clearly see that the Emmy Award itself depicts a feminine
angel with wings that are shaped like lightning bolts.
and we all know these lightning bolts are huge huge satanic symbols because for when Lucifer
fell from heaven he fell as lightning and became satan and we see this feminine angel holding
what looks like a globe or a planet or a star and this is truly plasmas and satanic.
Now, the occultist belief that Lucifer has a feminine energy to him, and that he can
also symbolize Venus, which is the morning star, and that Lucifer is a light bearer.
Now, it might be very odd to think of Lucifer as a female, but any encyclopedia will surely
tell you that occultists, and I repeat, occultists and Romans consider
Lucifer as Venus, which is in fact a very, very feminine energy.
Consider this, my brothers and sisters.
Satan often comes as a very attractive woman to deceive men.
Also, we see the Beatles song Lucy in the Sky with Diamonds is not only related to drugs and LSD,
but is also a veiled reference to Lucifer as Venus or the Sun.
We have even seen Scarlett Johansson.
play in the movie Lucy last year which had very occult and satanic references. Lucy or Lucy Ver,
the light bearer, could then also represent the Columbia Pictures logo and the Statue of Liberty
which was modeled after the Colossus of Rhodes which was the statue of the Greco-Roman Titan
And one of the biggest tools in the hands of the masters who run this world is Hollywood.
Hollywood is an incredible story.
I've said this, and maybe many hearing me now have heard me say this, but I'll say it again,
that the white man's establishment comes from Europe,
Well, all four, all northeast, south, and western Europe, even at the time of the Roman
Empire and before, that whole section of Europe that we call the center for the white man's
presence on the earth was quite literally ruled over.
Ancient Europe was ruled over by a priesthood called the Druids.
And the Druids, they were the ministers, the priests, the judges, the lawyers, they were the religious leaders.
So there was a priesthood that dominated Europe.
It still does. Europe is still a Druidic country, and America is a Druidic country.
Unless you understand the Druidic system, then you're never going to figure out what's going on in America and England.
But one of the most important symbols in the Druid system was a magic wand, like Merlin,
the magician with the magic wand.
And also the orchestra leaders and conductors always have a magic wand, and you have better
played the tune of the master.
He directs you to play, and he directs you to stop with the magic wand.
So you're dancing to his music.
Okay?
Magic Wands were always made out of the wood of a holly tree.
It's made out of hollywood.
And hollywood is a druidic establishment.
And the symbols, the words, the terms, the stories...
That cast the spell on you!
So that people go out on the movie and think in their minds,
this is the way you normally would react to a situation,
the way the guy in the movie did.
And so that's why today, in the Western civilization, especially in the West, our ability to work
with each other and live together as humans is so screwed up, because we've been watching
so much television and so many movies and so much silliness coming out of Hollywood,
so much violence and sex and drugs and all the rest of it that people have no idea in
the world how to live anymore, they've lost their humanity.
And in the process, they seek to transform the rest of mankind into carbon copies of themselves.
The television is used as the master instrument for brainwashing the rest of mankind.
Who have made paths with the devil.
That's right. The more accurate we're describing it would be that they have indulged themselves in the worship.
And they lead perfectly, they lead perfectly normal lives.
They travel, they're prominent in their own way,
but they do have this indulgence.
Father, here's a part of that I can never understand
that has never made sense to me.
And that is, if somebody were to make a pact with the devil,
Obviously, the implication is if the devil is there to make a pact with them to make a deal, to make their life, this short mortal life on earth, pleasurable, with money or women or travel, or more interest, or whatever it is they want, then they are aware of the presence of the devil, and they are obviously aware then.
of the presence of God as well, and they nevertheless make a conscious, stupid, short-term blind choice
to take what they can get in this lifetime.
And I just, to embrace one, you must embrace the other.
It's not like it's some wishy-washy person.
I know, I know, I know you do.
It is very not easy to understand except when you talk with them.
when they let their hair down and peel grapes, as we say,
and when they're on their way to being cured of what they're
or healed, is the proper word, you find that
there's an exhilaration and a faction which is both sensual and sexual
and mental when they're really indulging
in Luciferian worship. There is a
a peculiar exhilaration.
Like a drug then?
Yes.
You're doing really well now,
but didn't you release a CD like almost 10 years ago?
Yeah, I mean, I released a gospel record when I was 15
because I grew up in a household
where all I ever did was listen to gospel music
and my parents are both traveling ministers.
And so I kind of sang about what was going on in my life at 15.
That's how I got introduced to the music industry.
I swear I wanted to be like the Amy Grand of music.
Yeah.
But it didn't work out, and so I sold myself to the devil.
When they really indulge in Luciferian worship,
there is a peculiar exhilaration.
Like a drug, then?
Yes.
If I were the devil.
If I were the Prince of Darkness, I'd want to engulf the whole world in darkness,
and I'd have a third of its real estate and four-pits of its population,
but I wouldn't be happy until I had seized the ripest apple on the tree.
The.
So I'd set about however necessary to take over the United States.
I'd subvert the churches first, I'd begin with a campaign of whispers,
with the wisdom of a serpent I would whisper to you as I whispered to Eve.
Do as you please.
To the young I would whisper that the Bible is a myth, I would convince them that man
created God instead of the other way around.
I would confide that what's bad is good and what's good is square.
And the old I would teach to pray after me, our Father, which art in Washington.
And then I'd get organized. I'd educate authors in how to make lurid literature exciting so that anything else would appear dull and uninteresting.
I'd threaten TV with dirtier movies, and vice versa. I'd peddle narcotics to whom I could. I'd sell alcohol to ladies and gentlemen of distinction.
I'd tranquilize the rest with pills. If I were the devil, I'd soon have families at war with themselves, churches at war with themselves, and nations at war with themselves, until each and its turn was consumed.
and with promises of higher ratings, I'd have mesmerizing media panning the plane.
If I were the devil, I would encourage schools to refine young intellects,
but neglect the discipline of oceans just like those run wild.
Until before you knew it, you'd have to have drug-snipping dogs and metal detectors in every
schoolhouse door. Within a decade, I'd have prisons overflowing,
I'd have judges promoting pornography, and soon I could evict God from the courthouse,
then from the schoolhouse, and then from the houses of Congress, and in his own churches
I would substitute psychology for religion, and be of my science.
I would lure priests and pastors into misusing boys and girls, and church money.
If I were the devil, I'd make the symbol of Easter and egg, and the symbol of Christmas
a bottle.
until I had killed the incentive of the ambitious.
And what'll you bet?
I couldn't get whole states to promote gambling
as the way to get rich.
I would caution against extremes
in hard work, in patriotism, in moral conduct.
I would convince the young that marriage is old fashioned,
that swinging is more fun,
that what you see on TV is the way to be.
And thus I could undress you in public and I could lure you into bed with diseases for which there is no cure.
In other words, if I were the devil, I'd just keep right on doing what he's doing.
Well, hello everyone. I'm taking a walk today in the Hollywood Hills.
Am I in the United States of America? I hear you ask. No, I'm just on the outskirts of Rome.
These are the Hollywood Hills. No joke.
This place is called Nemi, which in Latin is Nemus.
Or the Holy Wood.
You see how all the trees in the hills are very, very ironically similar to the United States Hollywood in California.
I think you could pretty much just insert the American Hollywood sign.
right in the middle of that grove, and it wouldn't look much different to what we see on television.
Also that lake right in the centre, that's called Diana's Mirror, which emperors used to sail into
to assert themselves as stars. You would not believe just how many roads lead to Rome.
It really makes you think, I mean, the whole thing is a bit like a net, isn't it?
It's like a trap, it's a snare, that they would sail into these waters
and then, unbeknown to them, they're actually being lured in by its beauty
and they were to be sacrificed in the Temple of Diana.
Sounds a little familiar, doesn't it, with the Hollywood of today?
that it kind of lures us in with its impressiveness and its beauty and that really it's
Jezebel's net and
people are being
sacrificed
into it
people give their all to be in it and
people get brainwashed by it and they lose themselves to it
And people sacrifice so much, so much of their times, so much of their life to Hollywood.
It's exactly the same thing.
The amount, the sheer amount that Hollywood and the mainstream media have changed people,
have distracted people, have changed their lives, have made people more self-engrossed, encouraged self-worship.
has changed this world, has changed so many cultures and corrupted so many cultures across the whole world.
All from that one place, casting its spell over the viewers.
And sure enough, just off the coast of the water, the temple of Diana where they used to sacrifice.
The people that came into this water, so it's clear that the mother goddess worship was very prevalent in this area
The holy wood the worship of the huntress
You can see the bow and arrow symbolism everywhere
But no tellings what people used to do here
They quite literally used to sacrifice those people in this temple of Diana
Of course this is thousands of years old now, you can vividly picture really how evil this
pagan worship actually is, it's absolutely satanic, look at the fruits of it.
Now still, this is the mistake that some make, they think that this has all completely vanished
and this doesn't happen anymore, well the Luciferians, they are pantheistic, they worship
this old age of gods and goddess worship is still the new age religion it's
still part of the same thing it's it's not disappeared at all we've been very
blessed that Christian values spread across this world but you can see where
it will end up
When people fall away from true biblical Christian values of love and loving one another and loving Jesus and loving your neighbour and do not murder.
You can see where the world will go. It's not evolving, it's devolving back into the old age lies, but they're just calling it new.
So it can't be good when you look back at the past and see that this is still part of the same Luciferian religion
It can't be going anywhere good, can it? Because look at what used to happen
Do we want that again?
with most famous actors and actresses able to be so amazingly effective in convincing
in their performances.
That guy was so electrified that it came through the television.
How is it that they can move us to laughter, tears or anger at the drop of a hat?
Are they truly gifted with natural talent, as many suggest?
You see this and you're dazzled by their talent.
Do they possess a creative streak of genius that is unknown to most men?
possessed. Is it possible that these actors and actresses are possessed by demonic spirits
who have a specific agenda to fulfill? Oscar award-winning actor Denzel Washington told
60 Minutes exactly how he brings forth his best performances. Basically what I did was
got on my knees and sort of communicated with the spirits and when I came out I was in charge.
written that down and made a decision to play that.
What, are you going to smoke that?
Nope, you are.
Hell, if I am.
Yes.
You're Jesus-free.
The one-woman entertainment empire known as Oprah has strong affiliations with the demonic realm the most familiar face on television says you can not
Only use your body and physical self. This is how I see acting
I asked my body to be the carrier for the spirits of those who have come before me in a way that is most meaningful to the character
Just become the vehicle for that character calling out for these entities to take her over so that she may become a sparkling puppet
Oprah admits of her work before the camera
I tried to empty myself and let the spirit inhabit me.
With her global influence, her shows have become a smorgasbord for the New Age agenda.
You know, it's pretty interesting, isn't it, that this place is called Diana's Mirror
when Hollywood is all about self-obsession, self-worship. It's very interesting. You can see the same fruits.
in Hollywood today, Hollywood today, as we walk around this place which is called Nemi
which in Latin means Holy Wood, Diana and her Holy Wood.
The lake is called Diana's Mirror. So really when you think about it, Hollywood is just an extension
an artificial plastic version of what is already here. It's just a modern-day replica.
What is already on the outskirts of Rome all roads lead to Rome?
So really the one in the United States is like